<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog.atom"/>
  <title>Breizh Esthetics &amp; Salon Supply Co. - The Esthetician&apos;s Corner - Tips &amp; Tricks to Grow and Manage your Spa in Vancouver!</title>
  <updated>2018-02-01T14:48:00-08:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Breizh Esthetics &amp; Salon Supply Co.</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/see-you-at-the-2018-esi-vancouver-spa-tradeshow</id>
    <published>2018-02-01T14:48:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-02-01T14:49:02-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/see-you-at-the-2018-esi-vancouver-spa-tradeshow"/>
    <title>See you at the 2018 ESI Vancouver Spa Tradeshow!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Taylor Opheim</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>Super excited to announce that we will be back at the Esthetique Spa International Vancouver tradeshow this February 25th &amp; 26th! Come visit Corinne and myself as we perform demos of some best selling (&amp; most interesting) facial treatments! </span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/see-you-at-the-2018-esi-vancouver-spa-tradeshow">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Hello ladies and gents! Make sure to visit us at booth number 425!</p>
<p><a href="http://vancouver.spa-show.com" title="Vancouver Esthetics Spa International Tradeshow 2018"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/ESI_2018_banner.JPG?v=1517522390" alt="Esthetique-Spa-International-Tradeshow-Banner-2018-Vancouver" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></a></p>
<p>Super excited to announce that we will be back at the Esthetique Spa International Vancouver tradeshow this February 25th &amp; 26th! Come visit Corinne and myself as we perform demos of some best selling (&amp; most interesting) facial treatments! Furthermore we'll have tester products galore, a new catalog, and a huge 20x20 booth this time around! Why are we going for such a big booth, well we've got a few of our vendor partners coming with us ;)</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="www.breizh.ca" title="Breizh Beauty &amp; Spa Supplies Vancouver"><img alt="Breizh-Spa-Beauty-Supply-2018-Logo" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Breizh_Logo-PNG-2018_large.png?v=1517524988" style="float: none; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></a></p>
<p>In the first corner, we have... ourselves! You'll be able to watch some amazing facials that offer a direct benefit, while also trying out some of our best selling products. We won't have any physical stock with us, but we will definitely have TONS of samples, and be able to process your order and have it delivered to you the day after the show! I mean do you really want to carry around all the stuff you buy? Oh and we'll also have some goodies &amp; Breizh swag for the first visitors ;)</p>
<p><a href="https://bioseaweedgel.myshopify.com/" title="Bio-Seaweed Gel &amp; Beyond Vegan Polish Canada"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/M-Bio-Seaweed-Artiste-1_large.jpg?v=1517524915" alt="bio-seaweed-gel-artiste-polish" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></a></p>
<p>Second up, we have Bio-Seaweed Gel &amp; Beyond Vegan Polish (who will be published on our site shortly...) who will have quite a number of demonstrators and colors for you to try out and follow-up with a quick paraffin dip using our Therabath Medical Paraffin machine &amp; wax! A fabulous reason to stop by our booth. </p>
<p><a href="http://www.lipskin.ca/" title="Lipskin Permanent Cosmetics Kelowna Courses  &amp; Education"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/lipskin-slider_large.jpg?v=1517524877" alt="Okanagan-permanent-cosmetics-academy" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></a></p>
<p>Thirdly, we have two of our favorite permanent makeup &amp; lash extension educators coming in from the Okanagan, Cori Blasetti &amp; Karen Anderson of Okanagan Lash &amp; Brow Academy (also known as Lipskin &amp; Softap Permanent Cosmetics for those of you who met them last year (they were our neighbors)) who will have course and product information with them.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><a href="https://spray-tanning-kelowna.com/" title="City Chic Spray Tanning &amp; Education Kelowna"><img alt="sunless-rx-spray-tan-machine-kelowna" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Screenshot_2018-01-04-21-58-20-1_large.png?v=1517524817" style="float: none; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></a></p>
<p>Finally but not least, a third favorite educator from the Okanagan, Nanci Spencer with Spray Tans Canada! She'll be joined by the manufacturer of the Sunless Laser Tan System Mark Yacullo who invented this ingenious, and incredibly accurate spray tanning system. Personally I have been sprayed by these guys for the last two years since Breizh started going back to the show, and the result is always phenomenal! (Like "I just can't stop staring at myself in the mirror" phenomenal. They will have a tent setup so that spray tans can be done at the show (again I highly recommend this, it's like tanning but without the leathery after-effects...) so after you get your nails done, learn the benefits of permanent cosmetics, &amp; put on a little facial product, you can seal it all together with a beautiful new tan!</p>
<p>Here's the map of our booth for this year:</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Tradeshow_Booth_2018_ESI.JPG?v=1517524206" alt="Esthetique-spa-interntational-tradeshow-booth-breizh-2018-vancouver" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Make sure you pick up your tickets as soon as possible to get the best price for your two days at the <a href="http://vancouver.spa-show.com" title="Esthetique Spa International Tradeshow Vancouver Website">Esthetique Spa International Tradeshow Vancouver</a> by clicking the link!</p>
<p>OH and also at some point or another, I'm doing a presentation on "The Future of the Spa Industry - Where We'll be in 20 years". If someone could tell me what time I'm doing that, that'd be great... lol ;P</p>
<p>Hope to see you there!</p>
<p>Taylor</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/a-new-evolution-of-breizh-bye-bye-main-street</id>
    <published>2017-10-16T17:24:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2017-10-16T17:28:38-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/a-new-evolution-of-breizh-bye-bye-main-street"/>
    <title>A New Evolution of Breizh – Bye-Bye Main Street</title>
    <author>
      <name>Taylor Opheim</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><strong>History:</strong></p>
<p>In November of 1999 Breizh took possession of this Main Street heritage building built in 1926. A grand total of almost 20,000sqft, shared among 4 different businesses, has allowed us to operate a successful beauty supplies shop that had at one point, definitely been number one in the industry for quality and service. With over 25 professional beauty and spa cosmetics, supplies &amp; equipment brands available through our store having all this additional space gave us a lot of different options.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/BreizhBuilding_ea8ff8da-0cfa-4956-99e2-9fa2a49898e6_large.jpg?v=1508199963" alt="Breizh-Main-Street-Office"></p>
<p>Now with the rising costs of property and increased costs of upkeep and marketing, we need to change. This age old dinosaur (in business &amp; technology terms at least) needs to be updated to something slimmer, more streamlined and sexier to our customers and prospects. You can expect to see many different changes at Breizh in the coming months in how we service your business.</p>
<p><strong>New Model in the New Age:</strong></p>
<p>With the advent of the internet and ecommerce, you, our clients are now ordering mostly online, through email or just over the phone! As nice as the shop is it no longer makes sense with the technological advantages that could be had by letting it go. For the time being Breizh will not have a permanent physical location, instead focusing on better serving our clients and increasing the availability of our offerings. This move will allow us to better track inventory and performance, while allowing us to completely eliminate back orders for good.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/ecommerce-for-spa_large.jpg?v=1508200075" alt="ecommerce-for-spas-in-vancouver"></p>
<p>Not having to maintain &amp; manage the shop every day means we have more to spend with you supporting you in your shop. You might find me (Taylor) popping by with your deliveries more often than before as with this move, we’ll be completely mobile.</p>
<p>This also means we’ll be able to invest in some more innovative marketing &amp; a faster supply chain. Some really cool ideas are starting to surface already...</p>
<p><strong>Ordering:</strong></p>
<p>With this change it does mean that physical pickups of product orders will no longer be possible. All orders will be sent by delivery or post to you. Talk with us over the phone, through email, on our social channels, at our events, or by placing an order direct through our website. Coming soon we’ll also have a mobile app for you to access us even easier!</p>
<p>Transactions will still be done via credit card, paypal, etransfer, cheque or cash, although a COD charge may apply when paying cash or by cheque. Avoid this by sending an E-transfer for your bill!</p>
<p><strong>Events + Training:</strong></p>
<p>You’re probably wondering how this is going to happen. Since we’re eliminating the physical location, in preference of an online, mobile setup we’re going to be partnering with some of our clients to offer our demos in spa as educational partners and flagship businesses. Let us know if you’d like to become one as it will come with a bunch of free perks! Email me at <a href="mailto:Taylor@breizh.ca">Taylor@breizh.ca</a> if interested in becoming a flagship spa!</p>
<p><strong>Benefits:</strong></p>
<p>So really what are the main benefits to you here? In summary this change will:</p>
<ul>
<li>Get your orders done faster, more accurately</li>
<li>Eliminate your back orders completely</li>
<li>Give you more consistent follow-up</li>
<li>24/7 access to our inventory</li>
<li>Allow us to better personalize your service</li>
<li>Provide you better, more interesting education</li>
<li>Above all, ensure your clients constant satisfaction.</li>
</ul>
<p>It is happening relatively quickly and we’ll definitely be reaching out over the phone or in person to discuss with you how things will be working together going forward! We’re extremely excited about the new synergies we’ll be able to bring to you!</p>
<p>Cheers &amp; have a fabulous day!</p>
<p>Taylor</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/5-benefits-of-using-salon-solution-environmental-green-cleaner-put-this-stuff-on-everything</id>
    <published>2017-10-06T12:43:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2017-10-06T12:50:44-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/5-benefits-of-using-salon-solution-environmental-green-cleaner-put-this-stuff-on-everything"/>
    <title>5 Benefits of Using Salon Solution Environmental Green Cleaner: Put this… Stuff on Everything!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Taylor Opheim</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Hello again everybody! Today I want to talk to you about a new item that will CHANGE THE WAY YOU WORK! Both at home and in the spa! If you’re currently using anything like Method, Mr.Clean, Fantastik, Tide Laundry, Bleach, Windex, or any combination thereof to clean your spa you need to read on. We now have a cost effective solution, that everybody can use on ALL OF THE ITEMS! Seriously this replaces basically everything else that you clean with.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Salon-Solution-Environmental-Green-Cleaning-Solution" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Salon-Solution-Banner_large.jpg?v=1507319242" style="float: none;"></p>
<p>Salon Solution is our newest offering in the way of hygienic maintenance products that is completely environmental, it is made using only 4 ingredients, 3 of which are plants, and the 4<sup>th</sup> is water! Diluted at a 10:1 ratio with water, this cleaning agent can be used on quite literally everything. What’s also great about this biodegradable cleaner is that it’s hypo-allergenic, non-flammable, &amp; non-irritating so you can use without gloves! Perfect for removing soils, oils &amp; greases from any surface, plus it smells fantastic!</p>
<p>Here’s a list of items that the inventor who created Salon Solution has used it on before bringing it to market:</p>
<p>"<em>Please be advised that dilution rates for any cleaner are only a guideline … a suggestion if you will.</em></p>
<p><em>Each application and location will be different, different types of grease or oils (especially in Salons &amp; Spas).</em></p>
<p><em>There will be different dirt or contamination loads and of course different timelines between cleans.</em></p>
<p><em>With that in mind I have personally cleaned the following ..</em></p>
<ul>
<li><em>Automobile engines at full strength to 50/50 with water … amazing!</em></li>
<li><em>Automobile interior mats, upholstery and all interior surfaces 50/50 to 10% solution.</em></li>
<li><em>Automobile exterior, rims, tires at a 50/50 mix and about 50ml per 4l of water to wash the entire exterior</em></li>
<li><em>Carpet cleaning … full strength for stains and minimal in the application tank.</em></li>
<li><em>Walls floors and counters usually about 100 ml per 4 litres of water.</em></li>
<li><em>Shower doors (glass) takes off most of the water stains at full strength</em></li>
<li><em>Shower stall walls and tubs … removes water stains as well as oils and soap film.</em></li>
<li><em>Grout in bathroom and kitchen tiles 50/50 squirt on and scrub with an old tooth brush … you won’t believe it.</em></li>
<li><em>Used on mirrors … at 50/50 it leaves them with an anti-fog effect. PLEASE NOTE that cleaning glass is tricky as you must use a very weak solution to prevent streaking.</em></li>
<li><em>Laundry … have used it as a pre-treatment for stains and ‘ring around the collar’. Also works as a laundry detergent at about 100 ml per load.</em></li>
<li><em>Works great on sinks, fixtures and back splashes.</em></li>
<li><em>There really is nothing that this product will not clean … SAFELY!!!</em></li>
<li><em>Try different applications and different dilutions to fine tune the process.</em></li>
</ul>
<p><em>The most amazing thing is that it is cleaning without harsh chemicals and is completely safe … even on people.</em></p>
<p><em>Hope this helps!"</em></p>
<p>And now for the other half of this blog! The 5 biggest reasons you should be using Salon Solution in your spa:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>Salon Solution is Super Economical!</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Get started with our Salon Solution Salon &amp; Spa Intro kit for only $9.95 for 1L of concentrate and a free spray bottle! Working with the previously mentioned 10:1 ratio, that gives you 10 litres of cleaning solution to use around your home, spa and salon! Compared to the alternative of buying all sorts of different cleaning products, this will save you hundreds of dollars over the course of the years!</p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>Salon Solution is Multi-Purpose!</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I mean if you haven’t gotten the point yet,  this stuff can be used everywhere in your salon. To narrow it down a bit, here’s a look at some common places you can use it in your spa business:</p>
<ul>
<li>All surfaces and floors</li>
<li>On your windows and mirrors</li>
<li>On vinyl, leather and upholstery of spa/salon furniture</li>
<li>Use on your linens, laundry, and as a pre-treatment for stains</li>
<li>Use on salon tools like flat irons and shears, and other equipment (not a disinfectant though!)</li>
</ul>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>Salon Solution is Good for the Environment!</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>By using ingredients based off of 3 different plants and some water as the filler, and recyclable and reusable plastic bottles, there is nothing about Salon Solution that can damage the environment.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>Salon Solution Smells Fresh!</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>I mean come on, would you use it if it didn’t also smell great? We’re putting it on everything sooo, yeah.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>Salon Solution is Safer for your Employees!</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>And finally, this little gem of a cleaner is fantastic for your employees! Due to the lack of harsh chemicals, your employees’ skin is safe from harm and they aren’t breathing in anything that will eventually do some damage. Living employees are the best employees!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="salon-solution-environmental-cleaning-solution" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/products/ss_medium.JPG?v=1506704801" style="float: none;"></p>
<p>So there you have it folks! You can give us a call directly to <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/1l-salon-solutions-every-surface-cleaner" title="Salon Solution the Green Every Surface Cleaner @ Breizh Spa &amp; Beauty Supply">get your special intro kit at a price of $5.95 or click here to buy online</a> and use code SALONINTRO at checkout only while supplies last!</p>
<p>Cheers,</p>
<p>Taylor</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/8-reasons-you-should-be-using-an-ipl-machine-in-your-spa-or-clinic</id>
    <published>2017-09-30T21:52:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2017-09-30T21:55:25-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/8-reasons-you-should-be-using-an-ipl-machine-in-your-spa-or-clinic"/>
    <title>8 Reasons You Should Be Using an IPL Machine in Your Spa or Clinic</title>
    <author>
      <name>Taylor Opheim</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Hi there! And welcome to another posting on the Esthetician’s Corner Blog, the place where Spa Owners learn the things that school probably didn’t teach them! In this post we’re going to be going over the main benefits associated with an IPL Machine vs a Laser Hair removal unit &amp; as well just generally looking at what these machines are capable of and how quickly they can do it. I mean it’s seriously impressive. So awaaay we go:</p>
<p> </p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>IPL is faster than laser, waxing or electrolysis…</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>When comparing effective time spent that you’ll be delivering the treatment IPL hair removal is WAY faster than anything else out there. Regular laser hair removal means eliminating every single hair on an individual level and even then it only permanent reduction in the hair regrowth, not an actual permanent removal. Furthermore these sessions can take hours to get through and be noticeably painful throughout.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>On the flipside, you have waxing which although offers relatively little permanent benefit can be done very quickly, over large areas, and if done correctly with little pain (although if you follow the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-blue-hard-wax" title="Cirepil Blue Hard Wax @ Breizh Beauty &amp; Spa Supply">3 step Cirepil Wax process</a>, your waxing can be painless!). These sessions should be over in about 15-30 minutes depending on what’s being done.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Cirepil Blue Hard Wax 400g Tin Stripless" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/products/20121018_-_Cirepil_400g_-_Blue_medium.jpg?v=1505800672" style="float: none;"></p>
<p>Third, we have electrolysis. This is the slowest method for removing hair, and it needs to be done on each individual hair, however it is the ONLY permanent form of hair removal. Even IPL can’t guarantee a permanent elimination of the hair. With electrolysis you’re likely to pay by the minute for your sessions so they can typically last quite a varying amount of time. Depending on your practitioner/your personal preferences, electrolysis can be somewhat painful or totally painless (depending on if they/you use a numbing cream). Another factor that will determine comfort levels is the type of filament that they’re using, personally we always recommend <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/ballet-sterile-disposable-needles" title="Ballet Electrolysis Needles @ Breizh Beauty &amp; Spa Supply">Ballet Electrolysis</a> needles . Gold and Insulated are going to be the most comfortable treatments, however stainless steel will offer the most value.</p>
<p>And then finally we have IPL. These guys cover a small area of hair with every flash, on our machines, those flashes come in at 1 flash per 1 second on our top end model, or 2.4 seconds on our lower end model. In other words we can remove all your hair in under 10 minutes (during a speed contest anyways). It’s  not totally permanent, but it’s way faster than anything else. Expect your sessions to be in an out in under 10 minutes.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Eurofeedback-Beauty-IPL-Anthelia-Adena-Speed" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Anthelia-Adena-IPL-Machines-Models.JPG?v=1505023613" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<ol start="2">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>IPL Machines can do more than one type of treatment:</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Lasers are just lasers, waxing is just waxing, and electrolysis is just electrolysis. They can only fulfill their one intended purpose. IPL machines on the other hand can do up to <strong>6 </strong>different types of treatments! Anti-acne,  photo-rejuvenation, varicose veins, dark spot removal, dark hair removal AND (in our case) light (blond, white &amp; grey) hair removal! Check out these results:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">For Acne Treatment:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Anthelia-Adena-IPL-Acne-Treatment" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/IPL-Anti-Acne-Treatment-Before-After-Results.JPG?v=1505022589" style="float: none;"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">For Dark Spot/Pigmentation Treatment:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/IPL-Dark-Spot-Pigmentation-Before-After-results.JPG?v=1505022584" alt="IPL-Anthelia-Adena-Dark-pigment-spot-treatment"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">For a varicose vein treatment:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/IPL-Varicose-Veins-Treatment-Results.JPG?v=1505021474" alt="IPL-Adena-Anthelia-Varicose-Vein-Machine-Treatment"></p>
<p> </p>
<ol start="3">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>IPL Treatments are very low cost making them super profitable:</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Another super important factor for any business is the bottom line, the profits. Although the high price tag of an IPL machine can seem prohibitive… you have to remember your only paying about 0.05-0.12$ per flash. If you do a full back hair removal, it should take you about 400 flashes to get the job done. This means your total cost will be from $20-$48 depending on how you purchase your flash packs (discussed below). For a job like this you should charge your client roughly around the $300-$400 mark because you can’t forget about your other costs.</p>
<p>Other costs to remain aware of, your hourly wage (super important), your monthly space rent, the cost of any additional products used in the treatment, the marketing costs you put into the treatments, and of course the cost of the machine itself!</p>
<p>Now then going back to point #1 of how quick an IPL machine can work, most of your appointments should be about 10 minutes long by the time consultation and setup for the treatments is done.  If you work a full 8 hour day, and you take a 1 hour lunch, that still leaves you with 42 ten minute slots to fill with clients. It definitely make even more sense if you have an assistant or receptionist to help people check in and sell the complimenting retail items. But even if you did half that amount, you could still be turning out up wards of $1000 per day if you’re only doing $50 services!</p>
<p>Another great way that we see a lot of IPL owners making the big bucks, is by selling packages of services and getting clients to pre-book their next 5-10 sessions. Get in touch with our office to find out more about <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/efb-beaute-ipl-skin-rejuvenation-machines" title="Eurofeedback Anthelia &amp; Adena IPL Machines @ Breizh Beauty &amp; Spa Supply">our IPL profitability study</a>.</p>
<p> </p>
<ol start="4">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>IPLs are pay as you go:</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>What’s also great about these machines is they are designed for the casual users as well as the full-time professional. In order for the IPL to function, flashpacks need to be purchased (60,000 flashes are always included with your first purchase of the machine) in order to re-stock. The number of flashes available can always be seen in the settings menu of your IPL machine. This allows you to optimize your business costs based on your actual usage of the machine. Regardless of treatment type flash charges are the same price and type.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>IPL Machines are generally safer:</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Using an IPL on your clients, means you’re not concentrating light for a lengthy period of time, a quick one second flash, and it’s over, preventing any burns from happening. In our EuroFeedBack Anthelia &amp; Adena models, we have a special Energy Compensation system that allows for a perfect flash every single time. IPLs who don’t have this feature fade over time and take longer to complete the flash. Because of their adjustability, &amp; patented double filter system (that only allows the correct light to shine through), they’re able to be used on any skin type. These things seriously have a lot of patents on them, 24 in total to be exact. </p>
<p>In terms of design, any good IPL (not just ours) should be using squared pulses of light. Of course ours do, but the reason this is important is because it allows us to better regulate the flashes coming out of each handpiece. When it comes to machines not using squared pulses, here's what can and will happen over time:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Good-vs-bad-IPL-comparison-squared-pulse" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Good-Bad-IPL-Pulses_large.JPG?v=1506833373" style="float: none;"></p>
<ol start="6">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>IPL Machines are reliable… well at least ours are:</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Our EFB Anthelia &amp; Adena IPL’s are top of the line when it comes to reliability! EFB (the manufacturer) guarantees a 95% efficiency rate over the ENTIRE lifetime of the hand-pieces (the parts that administer the flash) thanks to their patented Energy Regulating System, Xenon lamps (that never degrade in efficiency), integrated water cooling system and 8 more patented secret technologies that they won’t tell us about, these things are basically infallible. Furthermore they’re backed by a full end to end 2 &amp; 3 year warranty!</p>
<ol start="7">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>IPL Machines come with Health Canada Certified Training:</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Unlike many “certifications” out there our fully included 2 day training with an IPL Expert is included with the purchase of any machine AND Is Health Canada Certified! The course is half theory, half practice so by the end of it you or your staff should be super comfortable to work right after the training. Additional training can be had at an additional cost if future employees also need to be trained.</p>
<ol start="8">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>EuroFeedBack IPL Machines can also handle blonde &amp; white hairs:</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>Hahaha and THIS is our trump card over every other form of IPL or Laser hair removal device! EFB Anthelia and Adena machines are THE ONLY IPL machines in the world that are capable of removing blond, white &amp; grey hairs. How do they do this? Well it looks a whole lot like normal hair removal, however through a special patented process, it does everything differently. I’d love to give you the juicy details, but because it’s a patented secret sauce there’s not a lot more to say other than these two machines can do it and others can’t because most laser/light based hair removal because of the lack of melanin (pigmentation) in the hair follicles. True story.</p>
<ol start="9">
<li>
<strong> </strong><strong>EuroFeedBack IPL Machines can also get “Global Over-Air” updates for Software:</strong>
</li>
</ol>
<p>BONUS fact! Certain of our IPL machines are specially equipped from the manufacturer with the ability to receive updates over the air via a wifi connection. This means no matter where you are in the world, your Adena model can receive the latest software version without any manual work! This feature will also soon be available on the Anthelia models as well! This helps to further improve and optimize the machines based on the feedback received from every other model equipped with the same technology. It’s a lot like those fancy Tesla cars!</p>
<p> </p>
<p>So there you have it folks, 9 reasons why every spa, salon or clinic should be using an IPL machine. Expensive, but a worthwhile investment when you consider how much time and money your saving to give your clients the best treatments. Of course the effects provided by the IPLs are also perfectly complimented when using good skin care. Keep up that retail ladies and gents!</p>
<p>For a bit more information on our EFB Anthelia and Adena models , <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/efb-beaute-ipl-skin-rejuvenation-machines" title="Breizh IPL Machines EFB Anthelia &amp; Adena">check out this page</a> or watch the video below:</p>
<p> <iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bXjj5hjBA0k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/the-best-marketing-tool-for-any-service-based-business-royaltie-gems</id>
    <published>2017-08-02T15:21:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:16:59-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/the-best-marketing-tool-for-any-service-based-business-royaltie-gems"/>
    <title>The Best New Marketing Tool for Any Service Based Business: Royaltie Gems</title>
    <author>
      <name>Taylor Opheim</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;">Before you begin, watch this short video! </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4y7cQNhwju0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
<p>Stop letting people walk past you without seeing you!</p>
<p>Hi there! How are things going with your current marketing? Is it leading customers directly to your booking or services page every single day, 24 hours a day? Are people passing by your spa, salon, or skin care business and not noticing it? Let’s hope it’s because they’re looking at their phone! I’ve recently discovered the next BIG thing in spa and salon marketing. Check this out:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Royaltie Bluetooth Beacon Gems</strong></p>
<p><strong><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/beacon-image_large.png?v=1501711243" alt="royaltie-beacon-gem-bluetooth-marketing-tool" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></strong></p>
<p>Meet your new best friends. By the end of this article, your whole family might carrying one of these little guys around. Here’s why: Imagine being able to market to every Android Smartphone within 100 meters of the Gem. This is what this does. Using Bluetooth technology this weatherproof, smart device is able to broadcast a message and a link to whatever webpage you like whenever someone is within the 100 meter proximity. But you can take these anywhere. In your car, in your purse, in the office, in your pocket, in your partner’s pocket, in your mother’s car… the list goes on as to where you can find somewhere to place one of these tiny devices. </p>
<p>Furthermore they’re just getting into the market and people are already having HUGE results! What’s great is they’re also very affordable for just about any small business, with plans starting at only 25$! They scale up nicely from there with a family pack of 8 available for 99$/month which is the best value by far!</p>
<p>For the techies out there, here are the device specifications for the Royaltie Lead Gem:</p>
<p><strong>Signal Range:</strong> 100m<br> <strong>Communications:</strong> Bluetooth Low Energy wireless technology 2.4GHz RF<br> <strong>Sensitivity:</strong> Bluetooth: -93dBm<br> <strong>Transmission Power:</strong> Bluetooth: -30dBm to 4dBm<br> <strong>Battery Life:</strong> Up to 2 years<br> <strong>Main Processor:</strong> 32-bit ARM® Cortex™ M0 CPU core<br> <strong>Bluetooth Processor:</strong> Nordic nRF51822<br> <strong>Data Rates:</strong> 250kBs, 1Mbs and 2Mbs</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://www.royaltie.com/?af=breizh" title="Royaltie Gems 24/7 Bluetooth Marketing Beacons"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Royaltie_Specs.JPG?v=1501711323" alt="royaltie-gem-beacon-bluetooth-marketing-sizing-specs-review"></a></p>
<p>Most of that probably kind of just swooshes over your head like it does mine, but the key facts are the range of transmission, each gem has a range of 100 meters. That’s the width of a football field! Imagine what it would do to your business if you went to football or hockey game! The other big thing, is the 2 year battery life. You can leave Royaltie gems just about anywhere (as they are weatherproof if you “drop” it somewhere) and for 2 years from the day you get it, they are working for you to market your business.</p>
<p>Here’s what some business owners are saying about the Royaltie Beacon Bluetooth Gems:</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Royaltie-Testimonial-bluetooth-beacon-gem-marketing-landscaper-trades-handyman" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Royaltie-Gem-Testimonial-Review-Bluetooth-Beacon-Landscaper_large.JPG?v=1501711399" style="float: none;"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Royaltie-Gem-Testimonial-Review-Bluetooth-Beacon-for-Realtors_large.JPG?v=1501711385" alt="Royaltie-Testimonial-bluetooth-beacon-gem-marketing-realtor-real-estate"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Royaltie-Gem-Testimonial-Review-Bluetooth-Beacon-for-restaurants_large.JPG?v=1501711391" alt="Royaltie-testimonial-bluetooth-beacon-gem-marketing-restaurant-food-truck"></p>
<p>Pretty impressive stuff right? Now here’s where it gets super interesting for yourself as someone who might be considering bringing some of these gems in to market your spa or salon business. Royaltie Gems offers an incredible affiliate program that lets you earn a commission for referring people to the product, it’s free to join and we highly recommend it! Think of all the business owners and service providers that you know who could benefit from gem technology. The Royaltie gem is the perfect marketing tool for realtors, restaurants, anyone in network marketing, sales reps, personal trainers, any self-employed trades person, financial services agents, artists and SO MANY more! On top of your services income you could make an extra little bit of commission just by recommending these to someone who might need more marketing, more exposure or more business. I mean honestly, who couldn’t use more money right?</p>
<p>The real estate agent above who is using Royaltie gems is also a great example of modern challenges for business owners. I mean you almost have a website, you maybe have an app, and maybe you’re promoting yourself on places like Groupon (Breizh doesn’t recommend Groupon for spas, you need returning customers, stop selling yourself cheap, there are other ways to build your business. Like in this article: 17 tips to market your esthetics business) but not everyone is seeing these things unless they specifically look for them.</p>
<p>With Royaltie gems you’re able to have the benefits of a giant billboard, directly in front of your clients, in a very subtle way that just lets them know you’re there. And who knows how many people are overdue on their facial, manicure or pedicure service! I’m sure you’ve seen a few and been like “Oh honey, you need to come see me, I have a cream for that.”</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/android4.png?v=1501712390" alt="android-logo-png-transparent-royaltie-marketing-gem-bluetooth-beacon"></p>
<p>Android smartphones currently represent 60% of the smartphone market. That’s a huge number of people walking by you every day that could be seeing your business. Now they do need to have their Bluetooth on, which I think most of us do these days thanks to our cars, headphones or at home/in-office smart devices and the notification from the gems only appear when someone is within proximity. The gems actually piggy-back off of Google’s own location services technology that automatically alerts you about a local social hotspot or restaurant and sometimes asks you to review it, meaning that they will work anywhere in the world. If you have ecommerce enabled in your business, this could mean a complete shift in the way and people you do business with. Apple phones are currently unable to receive the signal, because Google wants people to be informed of the awesome places and services around them. What’s better than making a new connection right? If you do happen to own an Apple Iphone then don’t worry, you can still use the Royaltie gems you just won’t see your own notification.</p>
<p>Anyways, this is something I’m super passionate about and I think is going to be a game changer in the world of marketing tools. Some people I know won’t take advantage of this because it doesn’t feel right for them, but those who do will certainly have a huge edge over their competition! As the CEO of Breizh I’ve personally ordered 16 Royaltie gems to promote our services across the country, we are bigger than just BC ;).  If you have any questions, definitely feel free to reach out. We’ll be talking and reporting the results of the Royaltie gems in our businesses very soon!</p>
<p><a href="https://www.royaltie.com/?af=breizh" title="Royaltie Gems 24/7 Bluetooth Marketing Beacons">Click here to stop letting people walk past you without seeing you!</a></p>
<p>Cheers &amp; have a great rest of the day!</p>
Taylor Opheim<br> <em>CEO</em> <br><em>Breizh Esthetics &amp; Salon Supply Co.</em> <br><em>www.breizh.ca </em> <br><em>604-874-7455</em>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/electrolysis-the-only-permanent-hair-removal-solution</id>
    <published>2017-05-02T10:18:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:10-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/electrolysis-the-only-permanent-hair-removal-solution"/>
    <title>Electrolysis: The Only Permanent Hair Removal Solution!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Capture_large.JPG?v=1493745485" alt="" width="462" height="288"></p>
<p>Ready for the summer?</p>
<p><br>As an esthetician, this might be the best time of the year for you, as your business will be flooded with clients eager to remove unwanted hair to show up their new summer outfits.<br>Here at Breizh, we provide you with everything you need to satisfy your customers need. We have high-quality brands of sugaring and waxing, as well as all the supplies and tools you need to perform such treatments.<br>If you had used <a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/113566725-sugar-of-the-nile-is-here-all-natural-hair-removal-at-last" target="_blank" title="SOTN" rel="noopener noreferrer">Sugar of the Nile</a> or<a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/get-a-premium-depilatory-waxing-treatment-with-cirepil" target="_blank" title="Cirepil" rel="noopener noreferrer"> Cirepil</a>, you must already know how effective these lines are and how soothing and painless they are for your clients. The only inconvenience you can find on them is that they are not permanent. When you want to give your clients a permanent solution to stop hair growth, the only method there is on the market is by electrolysis.<br>There are many misconceptions about electrolysis, but the truth is that, when it’s performed by a professional and experienced esthetician, is almost painless and doesn’t leave any permanent scarring or even temporary marking.<br>Luckily for you, we have the equipment and tools you need to start giving this service to your clients, as well as some pre and post-depilatory lotions and gels that you can’t miss when giving the treatment.<br>Our Ballet Electrolysis Filaments are manufactured with both a precise pint and a mirror-like surface polish. The rounded, tapered point of the needle will assist the electrologist in locating the follicle opening, and upon insertion, the needle will slide smoothly and accurately to the base of the follicle to destroy it.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/ballet-sterile-disposable-needles" target="_blank" title="ballet" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Ballet-Epilationsnadeln-620x6201_large.jpg?v=1493744835" alt=""></a><br>We have three different types of needles in various sizes so that you can adjust to each of your client’s needs:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/ballet-sterile-disposable-needles/products/depilatory-ballet-gold-electrolysis-needles" target="_blank" title="gold" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Ballet Gold</a> needle is designed for customers with sensitive skin and nickel allergies. It’s made of 24 carat gold to reduce redness and swelling in the most delicate areas.</li>
<li>The <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/ballet-sterile-disposable-needles/products/depilatory-ballet-insulated-electrolysis-needles" target="_blank" title="Insulated" rel="noopener noreferrer">Ballet Insulated</a> needles are suggested for the longest treatments, as its medical-grade special coating allow smooth insertions to prevent discomfort for an extended period of time. They are particularly suited for clients that find the treatment uncomfortable.</li>
<li>The <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/ballet-sterile-disposable-needles/products/depilatory-ballet-stainless-steel-electrolysis-needles" target="_blank" title="steel" rel="noopener noreferrer">Stainless Steel</a> needles are sculpted from 18/8 nickel-chrome Swedish stainless steel; the same used in fine surgical instruments. Achieving smooth and precise insertions, it’s the best filament to use on clients with healthy skin.</li>
</ul>
<p>So now you now, if you haven’t started doing electrolysis treatments, now is a good time to start introducing your clients and yourself into.<br>We are always here to give you information about which products to get adapting to your specific business needs, and guide you to the best places where you could get trained for such practices. Also, at <a href="http://hairfreelife.com/electrolysis_hair_removal_guidebook/" target="_blank" title="hair free info" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hair Free Life</a> you can find some useful documents to know more about how electrolysis works, and some safety procedures to follow when performing it.</p>
<p>Hope this information was useful! Don't forget to<a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us" title="breizh"> visit our webpage</a> or give us a call if you are interested in getting into the electrolysis business. We are always here to help you :) </p>
<p>Hope to see you soon around here,</p>
<p>Cheers,</p>
<p>Mariana</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/footlogix-where-medi-meets-pedi</id>
    <published>2017-04-18T11:43:00-07:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:04-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/footlogix-where-medi-meets-pedi"/>
    <title>Footlogix: Where Medi Meets Pedi!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Group-Shot_large.jpg?v=1492541014" alt=""></p>
<p>If you offer pedicure treatments in your business, surely you’ve encountered numerous problems in your client’s feet that they are not even aware they have.</p>
<p>Luckily for them, they are now in your hands and you know how to make their feet look healthy and beautiful at the same time. And fortunately for YOU, you use <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/footlogix-professional-medical-foot-care" title="footlogix">Footlogix</a>, the world’s first and only Pediceutical foot care line!</p>
<p>Footlogix’s active ingredients are pharmaceutical-graded, and penetrate your skin fast, and deep, effectively targeting all skin conditions that are affecting your feet and causing you mild or severe troubles.</p>
<p>Here at Breizh, we offer you a variety of products from this clinically- developed line so that you can provide your clients the most efficient foot renewal, and the most comfortable pedicure treatment!</p>
<p>The best thing about Footlogix is that it can be used in diabetic clients, and it offers affordable treatments that can be performed at any spa and be continued at home for long-lasting results. </p>
<p>Beggin your pedicure treatment with the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-13-foot-soak-concentrate" title="13">Foot Soak Concentrate</a>, which softens calluses with its pH balanced formula, while providing anti-microbial properties. The Exfoliating Seaweed Scrub combines organic micro algae and essential oils to effectively polish your feet without harming them. The</p>
<p>The <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-18-callus-softener" title="18">Callus Softener</a> provides instant results on toenails and cuticles and doesn't need to be washed off after spraying it. And you can give a final touch to any pedicure with the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-19-foot-massage-cream" title="19">Massage Formula </a>mouse, using it for 5 to 7 minutes and leaving your client's feet silky soft!</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OD60eoVarkk?list=PLNeQc5Y9wxvIwsNFLPaHplrpIfRTu8bKc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
<p>If you wish to recommend your clients an ongoing treatment to keep their feet healthy and moisturized all day long, the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-2-daily-maintenance" title="#2">Daily Maintenace Formula</a> is the perfect mouse for normal to dry skins, while you can recommend the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-3-very-dry-skin" title="#3">Very Dry Skin Formula</a> to more severe dryness cases. And for the most extreme and driest feet on Earth, there's nothing better than the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-3-cracked-heel" title="3+">Cracked Heel Formula.</a> Apply it twice a day and in a few days, you'll start feeling the healing results of soft, uncracked skin. Use the DD Cream Mousse for very dry or sensitive skins. With its patented Dermal Integration Technology, it revitalizes, hydrates and smooths your feet with anti-microbial properties.</p>
<p>Footlogix specialty solutions also offer the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-4-cold-feet" title="4">Cold Feet Formula</a>, to improve the micro-circulation of your feet and help you to keep them warm; the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-5-sweaty-feet" title="5">Sweaty Feet Formula,</a> an astringent to help you reduce foot perspiration; the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-8-tired-legs" title="8">Tired Leg Formula</a>, with vasoactive properties to help you reduce leg fatigue: and two spray deodorants for <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-9-foot-deodorant" title="9">Foot</a> and <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-10-shoe-deodorant" title="10">Shoe</a> with oil and menthol to kill odor causing bacteria!</p>
<p>If you are looking to deal with microbial issues, the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-7t-nail-tincture-spray" title="7t">Nail Tincture Spray</a> targets toenails prone to fungal infections. The <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-7-peeling-skin-anti-fungal" title="7">Peeling Skin Formula</a> provides relieve to athlete's foot and itching skin, particularly in the soles area and between the toes. And the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/footlogix-7-rough-skin-anti-fungal" title="rough">Rough Skin Formula</a> moisturizes to prevent scaling and irritations. All these three products contain Spiraleen, the exclusive Footlogix anti-fungal formula!</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/footlogix-pediceuticals-brighton_large.jpg?v=1492541170" alt="" width="339" height="403"></p>
<p>Finally, if you are in need of files or any other tools to perform your treatments, don't forget to<a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us" title="breizh"> visit our webpage</a> or give us a call. You can also find the perfect <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/continuum-pedicure-equipment" title="continnum">pedicure chairs for your spa in here</a>! </p>
<p>Hope to see you soon around here,</p>
<p>Cheers,</p>
<p>Mariana</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/get-a-premium-depilatory-waxing-treatment-with-cirepil</id>
    <published>2017-03-10T13:50:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:08-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/get-a-premium-depilatory-waxing-treatment-with-cirepil"/>
    <title>Join the World of Happy Waxing with Cirépil, Our Premium Depilatory Line</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/all-purpose_large.png?v=1489182559" alt=""></p>
<p>For many years, <a href="http://www.removinghair.co.uk/benefitsofwaxing.html" target="_blank">waxing has been the preferred hair removal method</a> of most clients in the esthetics business. And it is not hard to see why: a high-quality wax doesn't only provide long-lasting results, but will reduce the pain to a minimum, will exfoliate the skin without damaging it, and will diminish the quantity and growth time of body hair.<br>Because here at Breizh we focus on distributing the BEST brands only, we are proud of our premium waxing line, Cirépil, by Perron Rigot.<br>For over 70 years, Perron Rigot has innovated the waxing market, with their expert's team laboratory in France, patenting more than 20 kinds of waxes including the first stripless wax, the first hypoallergenic wax, and the first low-temperature wax.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/R_D_Up_medium.jpg?v=1489086343" style="float: none;"></p>
<p style="text-align: left;">If you are joining the world of happy waxing with us, we recommend the following premium classic waxes:</p>
<ul>
<li>If you are already a Cirépil fan, you must know their most famous product, <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-blue-hard-wax" title="Blue">Cirépil Blue</a>. With its ultra fluid gel texture, is everyone´s favorite as it's capable of handling every type of hair while maintaining its fluent consistency throughout the treatment</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-blue-hard-wax"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/2013_Blue_800g_large.jpg?v=1489086409" alt="" width="196" height="308"></a></p>
<ul>
<li>If you have clients with sensitive skin, the best wax you can provide them with is the<a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-cristal-ocean-strip-wax" title="Cristal ocean"> Cristal Ocean</a>. It's transparent and scent-free complexion is designed to get rid of any irritation for a perfect treatment.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-cristal-ocean-strip-wax"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/20121018_-_Cirepil_400g_-_Cristal_Ocean_1_medium.jpg?v=1489086867" alt="" width="187" height="187"></a></p>
<ul>
<li>And for extra delicate areas, the best wax to use is <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-cristalline-hard-wax" title="Cristalline">Cristalline. </a>Also designed for sensitive skin, this hypoallergenic wax will prevent you from getting any uncomfortable reactions that could irritate your client's skin.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-cristalline-hard-wax"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/2013cristalline_medium.jpg?v=1489087267" alt=""></a></p>
<ul>
<li>The <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-ease-soft-wax" title="ease">Cirépil Ease</a> wax is specifically designed for clients with dry skins and thin hairs. With coconut oil as one of its main ingredients and its creamy texture, it removes even the shortest hairs while leaving a fresh sensation in your skin.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-ease-soft-wax"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/20121018_-_Cirepil_400g_-_Ease_1024x1024_c1b194b6-49fc-4081-ae42-1772bed20005_medium.jpg?v=1489087604" alt="" width="202" height="202"></a></p>
<ul>
<li>As its name indicates it, <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-escential-rose-hard-wax" title="Rose">Escential Rose</a> will surround you and your client in a flower fragrance with relaxing effects. Ideal for short and hard hairs, its flexible texture is ideal for recently shaved skins.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-escential-rose-hard-wax"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/2013escential_rose_1024x1024_1_medium.jpg?v=1489088397" alt=""></a></p>
<ul>
<li>Cirépil <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-forte-400g-tin" title="forte">Forte</a> is designed for the toughest hairs to get. Use this honey textured wax with almond oil do the hard job and get rid of your clients' coarsest hairs!</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/20121018_-_Cirepil_400g_-_Forte_medium.jpg?v=1489178648" alt="" width="190" height="190"></p>
<ul>
<li>If you are looking for an all-purpose wax, the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-eurose-hard-wax" title="Eurose">Eurose</a> is the ideal product for you. Its easy to apply texture will help you do any kind of depilatory job in every type of skin in a quick and efficient way, making sure not to leave any trace of wax residues after the treatment. </li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-eurose-hard-wax"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/2013eurose_medium.jpg?v=1489179101" alt="" width="188" height="251"></a></p>
<ul>
<li>Formulated with micro-crystalline and mica, <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-nacree-blanche-strip-wax" title="Blanche">Nacrée Blanche</a> adapts to the length of all hairs. Its creamy gel texture and luminous reflection make it a beautiful pearly white wax to use in any skin type.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/wax-cirepil-nacree-blanche-strip-wax"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/20121018_-_Cirepil_400g_-_Nacree_Blanche_1_medium.jpg?v=1489179836" alt="" width="204" height="204"></a></p>
<p>Now you know all our awesome waxes, but don't forget we are here to offer supplies and tools for you to cover the full depilatory treatment!</p>
<p>The <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/skin-care-cirepil-blue-lotion" title="Blue lotion">Cirépil Blue Lotion</a> is an essential part for before and after the treatment, as it's a gentle lotion low on alcohol that will cleanse your client's skin for their safety and comfort.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/waxing-cirepil-post-wax-refreshment-gel" target="_blank"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Cirepil_Antiseptic_Blue_lotion_250ml_medium.jpg?v=1489181945" alt=""></a></p>
<p>Before applying any wax on the skin, be sure to apply the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/skin-care-cirepil-jasmine-depilatory-oil" title="Jasmine oil">Jasmine Depilatory Oil</a> with a cotton pad to moisturize the area you are working on. This will prevent any possible damage and irritation and will leave a soft sensation for all skin types.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/waxing-cirepil-post-wax-refreshment-gel" target="_blank"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/PreDep_Jasmin_Oil_250ml_medium.jpg?v=1489181985" alt=""></a></p>
<p>After performing the perfect treatment, don't let your client go until you have applied the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/waxing-cirepil-post-wax-refreshment-gel" target="_blank" title="post wax">Post Wax Refreshment Gel</a> in their skin. Its fluid texture makes it ideal for a leg massage, as it provides a cooling and soothing sensation for the rest of the day.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/waxing-cirepil-post-wax-refreshment-gel" target="_blank"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Refreshing_Gel_250ml_8.8oz_medium.jpg?v=1489182102" alt=""></a></p>
<p>For when you are applying the wax, Cirépil has created the smoothest and most practical <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/supplies-cirepil-smooth-non-woven-strips" target="_blank">Non-Woven Strips</a>. As they are pre-cut, it will save you save time and material, while its size makes them ideal to use in every area of your client's body.</p>
<p>And to keep your working area free of all messy situations, the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax/products/supplies-cirepil-protective-wax-heater-collars" target="_blank" title="Collars">Protective Heater Collars</a> will get all the residues of wax you may accidentally drop from time to time, making it way easier to clean your heater after a long day.</p>
<p>If you have questions about which is the best wax for your clients, we invite you to<a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/cirepil-hard-soft-wax" target="_blank" title="cirepil"> check out catalog out</a> and to<a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us" target="_blank"> contact us</a> regarding any further questions. Remember we are always here to help :)</p>
<p>Hope to see you soon around here,</p>
<p>Cheers,</p>
<p>Mariana</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/soothe-joint-and-muscle-pain-with-a-therabath-pro-paraffin-bath</id>
    <published>2017-03-03T14:29:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:12-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/soothe-joint-and-muscle-pain-with-a-therabath-pro-paraffin-bath"/>
    <title>Soothe Joint and Muscle Pain with a Therabath Pro Paraffin Bath</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Have you ever get clients complaining about arthritis, bursitis, or any other conditions that cause chronic joint pain? </p>
<p>By offering your clients a paraffin treatment, you'll alleviate those troublesome symptoms, apart from easing some skin conditions like dryness or irritations. After using thermotherapy, your clients will be out of any pain, plus their skin will be soothed and rehydrated, and for sure you'll become their favorite esthetician!</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Therabath-TB6-Paraffin-Wax-Heater-Bath-Elbow_1024x1024_b7d84cde-7318-45ca-9765-4a0749d7b7cf_large.jpg?v=1488579440" alt=""></p>
<p>Here at Breizh, our all-time favorite paraffin line is <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin" target="_blank" title="Therabath">TherabathPro</a>. Its products, all produced in the USA, are designed for you to provide paraffin treatments in any specific area of your client's body:</p>
<p>The <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin/products/equipment-therabath-pro-paraffin-bath-heater" target="_blank" title="Bath">Paraffin Bath Heater</a> runs an "always safe" temperature range and maintains paraffin heated at 130<span>°</span> Fahrenheit for up to 24 hours. It's big enough for your clients to completely deep their hands, elbows, and feet it.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin" target="_blank"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Therabath-paraffin-wax-warm-apple-spice_1024x1024_dcd9d929-d023-49d8-a316-7243e1431a84_large.png?v=1488579525" alt="" width="204" height="204"></a></p>
<p>If you are covering larger or more complicated areas, you can use the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin/products/paraffin-therabath-application-strips" target="_blank" title="Stips">Paraffin Application Stips</a>. They are flexible, so you can wrap them around any part of the body; and will leave a clean skin free of residues after you remove them from the skin. For the face or the back, we recommend the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin/products/paraffin-therabath-facial-application-brushes" target="_blank" title="Brushes">Application Brushes</a> that come in two different sizes, adapting to your needs.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin/products/paraffin-therabath-facial-application-brushes" target="_blank"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/therabath-paraffin-facial-body-brushes_large.png?v=1488579547" alt="" width="207" height="207"></a></p>
<p>To hold the heat for a longer time, after dipping your hands and feet in the paraffin bath, cover them with the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin/products/paraffin-therabath-plastic-liners-for-mitts-boots" target="_blank" title="Liners">Plastic Liners</a>, and put them inside the insulated <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin/products/paraffin-therabath-plush-mitts" target="_blank" title="Mittens">Plush Mittens</a> and <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin/products/paraffin-therabath-insulated-boots" target="_blank" title="Boots">Plush Boots</a>, to relieve pain and stiffed muscles.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin/products/paraffin-therabath-insulated-boots" target="_blank"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/therabath-paraffin-insulated-boots_large.jpeg?v=1488579599" alt="" width="245" height="165"></a></p>
<p>Finally, to add a special touch to this awesome treatment, Therabath has <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin/products/paraffin-therabath-paraffin-wax-refills" target="_blank" title="Paraffin">11 different scents of paraffin refills</a> that will delight your senses! If you prefer, you can also order the unscented refill to use as it comes or to add an essential oil you already have in mind.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/paraffin/products/paraffin-therabath-paraffin-wax-refills" target="_blank"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Therabath-paraffin-wax-vanilla-cupcake_1024x1024_410640fc-2268-465b-8daa-c630ac996cc8_large.png?v=1488579663" alt="" width="231" height="231"></a></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>Another favorite practice that estheticians provide is applying a warm paraffin bath after a manicure or pedicure to pamper their clients, So now you now ;)</p>
<p>Let us know what your favorite paraffin scent is so we can place an order for you anytime!</p>
<p>Cheers,</p>
<p>Mariana</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/quantum-phytobiodermie-the-beauty-of-emotions</id>
    <published>2017-03-02T11:28:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:18-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/quantum-phytobiodermie-the-beauty-of-emotions"/>
    <title>Quantum Phytobiodermie: The Beauty of Emotions</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Wood_Model_large.jpg?v=1488482783" alt=""></p>
<p>After months of research, Phyto5 have managed to incorporate the concept of Quantum Physics into their Phytobiodermie line, creating a new awesome line that now offers the power of balancing emotions!</p>
<p>These new Quantum certified products consist on the 5 Phyt'Ethers, 5 skin toners, and 5 clays you already know, but that now have the power of working on your vital energy <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2014/oct/26/youre-powered-by-quantum-mechanics-biology" target="_blank" title="quantum mechanics">in the same way that Quantum Mechanics do</a>. Aiming to increase your happiness, the scientists that developed this concept know emotions are the roots of all conditions in your skin. That's why, though the formula you know remained the same, the line now works at deeper vibration levels.</p>
<p>In the traditional Phyto5 treatments, the esthetician is in charge of giving the client a proper skin diagnostic. Now, the client, now known as the <em>candidate</em>, is to choose one of 5 cards of emotions (confidence, joy, contentment, and serenity) at the same time they inhale the serum associated with each emotion. After this, the esthetician will treat the candidate after the card they select corresponding to their emotional state.</p>
<p>After the Quantum Diagnostic, all there's left to do is follow the Phyto5 treatment, relying on <a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/light-therapy-and-ayurveda-philosophy-in-phyto5" target="_blank" title="Light Therapy">Chromotherapy</a> to create an emotional symbiosis between the candidate and the professional to ensure positive results.</p>
<p>As the elements also work in seasonal cycles, we encourage you to look at this diagnostics as phases. Once you achieve your desired state of mind, move on to the next one to get all the benefits of balanced emotions! </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/phyto5-wood-line-get-rid-of-oily-skin-and-hyperpigmentation" target="_blank" title="Wood">The Wood Line</a> aims to balance Self-confidence. People who have ongoing projects will take advantage of this line, as it will provide them the courage and strength to succeed in their personal or professional tasks. Wood is the element of movement, so if all you need is something to boost your energy, this is the right line to start.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/soothe-your-body-with-the-phyto5-fire-line" target="_blank" title="fire">The Fire Line</a> balances Joy. It's important that now that you got courage from the wood element, celebrate your success and achievements and spread that happiness with family and friends.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/mineralize-dry-skin-with-the-metal-line-of-phyto5" target="_blank" title="Metal">The Metal Line</a> balances Satisfaction. In this phase, you would find the comfort of the material elements you've harvested during the previous elements. Metal is a time to enjoy the fruit of your efforts.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/tone-dehydrated-skin-with-phyto5-water-line" target="_blank" title="Water">The Water Line</a> balances Serenity. As Metal works for material beings, is also important to get detached of all what you don't need and find comfort in isolation. With this element, the cycle of emotions is completed, and you are ready to start over new projects again.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/purify-your-body-with-the-phyto5-earth-line" target="_blank" title="Earth">The Eath Line</a> is an element of both seasonal and emotional transitions. When the professional doesn't get a clear Quantum Diagnostic, the Earth element represents unfinished projects. This is a frequent line used in creative candidates and provides stability as they keep looking to satisfy their curiosity.</p>
<p>Keep always in mind that beauty is only a reflection of the emotions inside us. Well-being is essential for happiness, which is the primary cause of beauty and wellness in a surface level of our bodies!</p>
<p>If you have further questions after checking our <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/phyto-5" target="_blank" title="phyto5">Phyto5 catalog </a>out, please, don't hesitate to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us" target="_blank" title="Contact">ask for help</a>!</p>
<p>Cheers, </p>
<p>Mariana</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/avoid-uv-rays-all-year-long-with-pier-auge</id>
    <published>2017-02-23T10:44:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:21-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/avoid-uv-rays-all-year-long-with-pier-auge"/>
    <title>Avoid UV Rays All Year Long With Pier Augé</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge">Pierre J. Augé’s Base Dergyl</a><span> is a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement and balance the epidermis’ structure, adapting to the chemistry of each particular skin to restore its natural functions. </span><br><span>The ingredients on each of its lines are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</span></p>
<p><span>This time, we are talking about the two Pier Augé sun care products!</span></p>
<p>Though clients usually forget about wearing sunscreen during the winter, it's important for you to be aware of UV rays throughout the whole year. Without the proper protection, UVAs can penetrate deeply into your skin causing irreversible damage that breaks your collagen structures and accelerates aging. <a href="https://www.cancercouncil.com.au/63295/cancer-prevention/sun-protection/sun-protection-sport-and-recreation/sun-protection-information-for-sporting-groups/how-ultraviolet-uv-radiation-causes-skin-cancer/" target="_blank" title="skin cancer">Don't forget that UV rays are the main cause of skin cancer.</a></p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/pier-auge_large.jpg?v=1487875327" alt=""></p>
<p><span>So, it doesn't matter if it's still cold outside, we highly encourage you to wear sunscreen all year long whenever it's sunny outside!</span></p>
<p>Pier Augé's <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-anti-spot-sun-care-ip-50" target="_blank" title="sunscreen">Anti-Spot Sun Care </a>it designed for every skin type. Its main ingredients contain Bear Berry, rich in antioxidants; Vitamin E, a powerful astringent; and minerals that diffuse UV radiation. Plus, its light texture is water-resistant and can be used with makeup.</p>
<p>If you've been hanging out all day under the sun, it's also important that after UV exposure you apply the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-soothing-after-sun-gel" target="_blank" title="Soothing Gel">After Sun Soothing Gel</a>. It contains Aloe Vera, which is widely known for containing the vitamins needed for your skin to be softened, healed, and repaired from redness and swollen.</p>
<p><span>These two treatments will also keep your skin hydrated all day long, and are the perfect complement to be used with your daily skincare routines!</span></p>
<p><span>As always, don't forget t</span>o <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us" target="_blank" title="Contact">ask for help</a> if you need placing an order with us ;) We are delighted to keep taking care of your skin everyday! </p>
<p>Cheers, </p>
<p>Mariana</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/get-paraben-free-with-piera-from-pier-auge</id>
    <published>2017-02-23T10:08:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:26-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/get-paraben-free-with-piera-from-pier-auge"/>
    <title>Get Paraben-Free With Piera from Pier Augé</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<br data-mce-bogus="1"><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/get-paraben-free-with-piera-from-pier-auge">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge">Pierre J. Augé’s Base Dergyl</a><span> is a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement and balance the epidermis’ structure, adapting to the chemistry of each particular skin to restore its natural functions. </span><br><span>The ingredients on each of its lines are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</span></p>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/piera_large.png?v=1487873350" alt=""></span></p>
<p>Today we are talking about Pier Augé's newest concept, its paraben-free line, Piera! </p>
<p>This line was created for clients who have opted to put more natural ingredients in their lives. Notice that though there are several public concerns about paraben, it has been proven that the <a href="http://cosmeticscop.com/2016/09/08/parabens-really-problem/" title="paraben">small amounts you get from your daily beauty products are not harmful to your body</a>. Nevertheless, Pier Augé has created this unique line to answer to their clients's requests! </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-piera-pure-cleansing-gel" target="_blank" title="Cleansing Gel">Pure Cleansing Gel</a></p>
<p>Remove impurities, pollution, and makeup from your skin with this light textured gel. Use it every morning and night to decongest, soothe, and defend your skin against bacteria.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-pure-soothing-piera" target="_blank" title="soothing">Pure Soothing</a></p>
<p>For the most delicate skin, this cream will soothe your skin and cure it of inflammation and redness. Because it promotes cellular respiration, it is also an excellent anti-aging treatment.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-pure-anti-wrinkles-piera" target="_blank" title="Anti wrinkles">Pure Anti-Wrinkle</a></p>
<p>Its name is self-explanatory. It decongests blood capillaries, promotes cellular respiration, restores your elasticity and moisturizes your skin, smoothing existing wrinkles and preventing new ones from appearing.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-pure-moisturizing-piera" target="_blank" title="moisturizing">Pure Moisturizing</a></p>
<p>A face cream designed for skins that lack water in their dermis. Rebuilds your defense system to keep your skin protected from external pollutants at the same time that it avoids the loss of epidermic water.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-pure-gel-mask-piera" target="_blank" title="Gel mask">Pure Gel Mask</a></p>
<p>Decongests your skin by using this mask one or twice a week.By just leaving it for 15 minutes, you'll feel your skin firmer, purified, softened, and protected.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-pure-eye-and-lip-contour-piera" target="_blank" title="eye and lip">Pure Eye and Lip Contour</a></p>
<p>The perfect firming treatment for those who feel the contours of their lips and eyes marked by tiredness and age. With its active ingredients of natural oils and minerals, you'll feel your elasticity restored and the contours of your face redefined after the firsts applications.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Let us know if you have any doubts about which of these treatments to get. Also, please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us">ask for help</a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</p>
<p>Cheers, </p>
<p>Mariana</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/pier-agues-antipollution-line-uniquely-designed-for-men</id>
    <published>2017-02-22T11:24:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:28-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/pier-agues-antipollution-line-uniquely-designed-for-men"/>
    <title>Pier Agué&apos;s Antipollution Line Uniquely Designed for Men</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge">Pierre J. Augé’s Base Dergyl</a> is a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement and balance the epidermis’ structure, adapting to the chemistry of each particular skin to restore its natural functions. <br>The ingredients on each of its lines are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/mensFaceProducts_large.jpg?v=1487791138" alt=""></p>
<p>Today, we are talking about the Men Antipollution Line!</p>
<p>As you probably know, <a href="http://www.dermalogica.co.uk/uk/yourskin/19_article_is_a_man_s_skin_really_different_from_a_woman_s_.html" title="Men vs women skin">men and women have different skin metabolisms</a>. Though this difference is often overlooked, Pier Augé has created a unique line to adjust to men's skin structures specifically.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-men-gentle-scrub-face-wash-gel" target="_blank" title="Scrub">Gentle Scrub Cleansing Gel</a></p>
<p>Controls the respiration of the skin while it deeply cleans it and exfoliates it. Dead cells and impurities are removed, leaving a clear and moisturized sensation on your skin.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-men-relaxing-treatment-mask" target="_blank" title="Mask">Relaxing Treatment Mask</a></p>
<p>Apply this mask once a week and leave it on for 10 minutes. You´ll notice it´s protective active ingredients restructuring your skin in seconds, and it will improve its elasticity, moisture, and softness immediately.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-men-anti-fatigue-eye-contour-gel" target="_blank" title="Gel">Eye Contour Gel</a></p>
<p>If your eyes look tired and swollen, this is the perfect treatment for you. This anti-tiredness moisturizer will smooth and firm the bags under your eyes, giving them a younger look while it purifies the skin.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-men-after-shave-ultra-matt-balm" target="_blank" title="After Shave">After Shave Balm</a></p>
<p>Everyone needs one of these right after shaving. With a powerful mixture of Vitamins and vegetable oils, your skin will be soothed and protected all day.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-men-hyper-hydrating-protective-care" target="_blank" title="Moisturizing treatment">Hyper Moisturizing Treatment</a></p>
<p>Its name says it all. Apply this cream every day and night to moisturize your skin and add anti-aging ingredients to your skin. It promotes cellular respiration and makes your skin more resistant against external pollutants.</p>
<p>Let us know if you have any doubts about which of these treatments to get. Also, please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us">ask for help</a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</p>
<p>Cheers, </p>
<p>Mariana</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/cure-dehydrated-skins-by-moisturizing-them-with-pier-auge</id>
    <published>2017-02-21T14:30:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:37-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/cure-dehydrated-skins-by-moisturizing-them-with-pier-auge"/>
    <title>Cure Dehydrated Skins by Moisturizing them With Pier Augé</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge">Pierre J. Augé’s Base Dergyl</a> is a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement and balance the epidermis’ structure, adapting to the chemistry of each particular skin to restore its natural functions. <br>The ingredients on each of its lines are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Pier_Auge_Group_picture_smaller_large.png?v=1487716936" alt=""></p>
<p>Today we are talking about the Intense Moisturization Program!</p>
<p>Remember that <a href="https://www.annmariegianni.com/dry-vs-dehydrated-skin/" target="_blank" title="Dry vs. dehydrated">dehydrated skins are the ones that lack water in the dermis, while dry skins are a sign of insufficient sebaceous secretion</a>. Now that we have those two problems defined, what we are covering in this post are the products that target dehydrated skins. <a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/soothe-dry-skins-with-pier-auge" target="_blank" title="Dry skin">Check this link out if you are looking for dry skin treatments</a> :)</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-cucumber-hydrating-cream" target="_blank" title="ental">ENTAL Super Hydratant</a></p>
<p>Targeted for juvenile skins, this treatment will bring the ideal balance of moisturization to your skin. With the help of cucumber and lanoline oil, this protective treatment will fresh and softer your skin all day long.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-energizing-vitamin-c-serum" target="_blank" title="vitamin c serum">Tempus Serum</a></p>
<p>Using vitamin C as its main active ingredient, this product is designed to energize your skin to fight the external threats responsible for your loss of water in the skin. Regain elasticity, firmness, and radiance by applying it daily before starting your skincare routine.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-ental-survitamine-dull-skin" target="_blank" title="Survitamine">Ental Survitamine</a></p>
<p>If your skin fills dull and itchy, you probably need this repairing emulsion. Make your skin softer and provide it with a rich mixture of vitamins to help it recover its firmness and radiance.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-le-soin-teint-tempus" target="_blank" title="soin tente">Le Soin Teinté</a></p>
<p>This treatment is a combo of two perfect creams to maintain the youth of the skin. Apply mornings and evenings to help your skin defend itself against pollution and stress, to bring back the perfect balance of water to your skin and maintain for the long term.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-hydrating-treatment-fondamental-dehydrated-skins" target="_blank" title="Fundamental">Moisturizing Fundamental Treatment</a></p>
<p>Stimulate your cell renewal process with this powerful cream. To get long lasting results, apply every morning and night, and restore the natural cutaneous metabolism that keeps your skin moisturized without the help of any extra treatments.</p>
<p>Let us know if you have any doubts about which of these treatments to get. Also, please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us">ask for help</a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</p>
<p>Cheers, </p>
<p>Mariana</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/get-rid-of-wrinkles-with-the-time-control-program-of-pier-auge</id>
    <published>2017-02-21T13:52:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:37-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/get-rid-of-wrinkles-with-the-time-control-program-of-pier-auge"/>
    <title>Get Rid of Wrinkles With the Time Control Program of Pier Augé</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge">Pierre J. Augé’s Base Dergyl</a> is a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement and balance the epidermis’ structure, adapting to the chemistry of each particular skin to restore its natural functions. <br>The ingredients on each of its lines are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Time_Control_Program_1_large.jpg?v=1487714008" alt=""></p>
<p>Today we are talking about the Time Control Program!</p>
<p>While wrinkles inevitably appear with age, some factors can make them appear way sooner than you were expecting. External factors like pollution, or internal ones like stress and tiredness, usually make your wrinkles more pronounced if you don’t have an accurate skincare routine.</p>
<p>These anti-aging products then, are also anti-wrinkles, meaning that they don’t only prevent wrinkles, but also reduce them.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-soin-unique-day-and-night-pa24" target="_blank" title="pa24">PA24 Day and Night</a></p>
<p>Apply this cream day and night to target your first wrinkles. By reproducing the natural moisturizing process of your skin and increasing cellular respiration, you’ll notice how the wrinkle formations in your skin slow down immediately.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-m2a-serum-anti-ageing-booster" target="_blank" title="regenerating">M2A Active Regenerating Serum</a></p>
<p>It’s active ingredient, Hibiscus extract, is widely known in the esthetic’s industry to fight all signs of aging. This serum can be used after your daily skincare routine, or act alone as a cream to combat dryness and stop the formation of pigmentation spots.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-intense-firming-serum" target="_blank" title="intense">PIER Intense Firming Serum</a></p>
<p>Fights cutaneous aging by helping in the process of tissue regeneration. Its antioxidant components fight against free radicals, increasing your levels of collagen that will redefine the natural oval shape of your face. In just a few days you’ll feel your skin firmer, smoother, and toner!</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-acma-re-densifying-treatment" target="_blank" title="Acma">ACMA Redensifying Treatment</a></p>
<p>Made specially for mature skins, brings back the ideal nutrition levels to your skin tissues with vegetable oils as active ingredients. Its astringent properties will oxygenate your skin, and its vitamin components will create a powerful moisturizing sensation on your skin. Your skin will be revitalized and fully protected.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-luminescent-revitalising-treatment-cream" target="_blank" title="fleurs">Fleurs d’Absolu</a></p>
<p>Its active ingredients are all extracts of eight flowers, all know for its anti-aging properties. Sunflower will add vitamins to your skin, as camellias soften it. Sacred lots will make your skin radiant, and iris will increase its tonicity. Let this flower power mixture to fight against wrinkles and pigmentations spots at the same time!</p>
<p>Let us know if you have any doubts about which of these treatments to get. Also, please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us">ask for help</a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</p>
<p>Cheers, </p>
<p>Mariana</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/soothe-dry-skins-with-pier-auge</id>
    <published>2017-02-17T11:35:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:39-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/soothe-dry-skins-with-pier-auge"/>
    <title>Soothe Dry Skins with Pier Augé</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge">Pierre J. Augé’s Base Dergyl</a> is a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement and balance the epidermis’ structure, adapting to the chemistry of each particular skin to restore its natural functions. <br>The ingredients on each of its lines are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Pier-Auge-Soothing-Ental-Delicate_large.jpg?v=1487359880" alt=""></p>
<p>Today we are talking about the Pier Augé Active Soothing Program, which targets dry skin.</p>
<p>Notice that dry skin is not the same as dehydrated. While its lack of water characterizes dehydrated, dry skin feels rough and itchy because of insufficient sebaceous secretion.</p>
<p>These treatments will restore the natural barrier of your skin to protect it against external pollutants at the same time it heals the dermis from the inside.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-completude-regenerating-tri-active-treatment" target="_blank" title="Completude">Complétude Regenerating Tri-Active Treatment</a></p>
<p>Designed for dry and sensitive skins, its actions include tissue regeneration, moisturizing, and protection against UV radiation. With its active ingredient of Borage Oil it acts against cutaneous dryness. You’ll see antiaging results from the very first application, and most important, your skin will be regenerated, protected, and full of vitality!</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-sper-ental-dry-skin" target="_blank" title="super ental">Super Ental</a></p>
<p>This complete revitalizing treatment acts on itchiness, restores elasticity, and decongest the blood capillaries. After applying this cream, you’ll feel moisturized, with a soothed and toned up tskin. Regain your firmness and radiance by supplying your dry skin with all the vitamins and proteins it needs!</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-ental-delicate" target="_blank" title="ental delicate">Ental Delicate</a></p>
<p>Apply this soothing treatment made for the most sensitive skins to repair your skin from dryness. This cream will correct the process of cell regeneration to restore your natural barriers, so you get rid of that uncomfortable, itchy sensation.</p>
<p><span>Let us know if you have any doubts about which of these treatments to get. Also, please don't forget to</span><span> </span><span><a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us">ask for help</a></span><span> </span><span>if you need placing an order with us ;)</span></p>
<p><span>Cheers, </span></p>
<p><span>Mariana</span></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/combat-pigmentation-spots-with-the-pier-auge-s-lightening-program</id>
    <published>2017-02-16T12:24:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:45-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/combat-pigmentation-spots-with-the-pier-auge-s-lightening-program"/>
    <title>Combat Pigmentation Spots with the Pier Augé’s Lightening Program!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge">Pierre J. Augé’s Base Dergyl</a> is a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement and balance the epidermis’ structure, adapting to the chemistry of each particular skin to restore its natural functions. <br>The ingredients on each of its lines are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/pier-auge-lightening-program_1024x1024_a992b69e-1fc1-45ad-9d37-4b4c1a465231_large.png?v=1487276801" alt=""></p>
<p>Today, we’re talking about the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-ekia-lightening-treatment-1" target="_blank" title="lightening products">Pier Augé’s Lightening Program</a>!</p>
<p>As we mentioned in one of our previous posts, melanin in our body’s natural defense against UV radiation. One of the most uncomfortable issues of excessive radiation is that it causes malfunctions on the production of melanin, making unwanted spots to appear on out skin.</p>
<p>This program will help your skin to combat hyperpigmentation, to make your skin look even and younger!</p>
<p><strong>Ekiá Serum</strong></p>
<p>This lightening serum controls the appearance of pigmentation spots and erases the existing ones. Its active ingredients contain antioxidants that fight free radicals, so apart of having a skin free of pigmentation spots, your collagen production will be restored.</p>
<p><strong>Ekiá Treatment</strong></p>
<p>Apply over the lightening serum to get long lasting results. This cream will regenerate your skin after getting rid of pigmentation spots and bring anti-aging active ingredients for you to look radiant.</p>
<p>After <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-ekia-lightening-treatment-1" target="_blank" title="treatment">this treatment</a>, the over pigmentation on your skin will be gone, and brown and black spots will be controlled and erased!</p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Let us know if you have any doubts on the program. Also, please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us"><span class="s2">ask for help</span></a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Cheers, </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mariana</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/heal-regenerate-and-reinforce-your-skin-with-pier-auge</id>
    <published>2017-02-16T11:27:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:17:49-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/heal-regenerate-and-reinforce-your-skin-with-pier-auge"/>
    <title>Heal, Regenerate, and Reinforce Your Skin With Pier Augé</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge">Pierre J. Augé’s Base Dergyl</a><span> is a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement and balance the epidermis’ structure, adapting to the chemistry of each particular skin to restore its natural functions. </span><br>The ingredients on each of its lines are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/specifique_50bc38f000d75_large.png?v=1487273178" alt=""></p>
<p>On this post, we are talking about the Specifics Line, which focuses on particular skin failures and reinforces the capacity of the skin to keep away those problems.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-ental-rimser-repairing-and-revitalizing" target="_blank" title="Ental Rimser">Ental Rimser</a></p>
<p>To be applied every morning and night and suitable for all kinds of skin. This skin revitalizer simulates the synthesis of collagen in your dermis to stimulate your immune system and bring back its natural defenses. Give your cells the energy to work at their best to prevent problematic conditions such as premature wrinkles, pigmentation spots, and enlarged pores.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-ental-rose-diffused-redness-regulator" target="_blank" title="Ental Rose">Ental Rose</a></p>
<p>Do you suffer from redness in your skin? This regulator helps irritated skins to combat climatic attacks, which are the first cause of inflamed skin. Get the perfect treatment for hypersensitive and blotchy skins and get rid of broken veins, itchiness, and redness!</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-eye-gel-pa24" target="_blank" title="Eye Gel">PA24 Eye Gel</a></p>
<p>Reduces the puffiness under your eyes and prevents the formation of wrinkles. Give your eye area the active ingredients it needs to regenerate and keep the elasticity of your skin. It also prevents the formation of pigmentation spots and redness, making every skin type to look younger.</p>
<p> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Let us know if you have any doubts on which treatment would work best for your clients. Also, please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us"><span class="s2">ask for help</span></a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Cheers, </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mariana</span></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/get-rid-of-skin-impurities-with-pierre-auge</id>
    <published>2017-02-15T12:20:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:00-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/get-rid-of-skin-impurities-with-pierre-auge"/>
    <title>Get Rid of Skin Impurities With Pierre Augé</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge" target="_blank" title="Base Dergyl">Pierre J. Augé’s Base Dergyl</a> is a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement and balance the epidermis’ structure, adapting to the chemistry of each particular skin to restore its natural functions. <br>The ingredients on each of its lines are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/pure_large.jpeg?v=1487190608" alt=""></p>
<p><br>Today we are telling you about the Pierre Augé’s Purifiers!<br>It’s important, first, to know that this line aims to different actions than the <a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/purify-your-skin-with-the-pier-auges-cleansers" target="_blank" title="Cleansers">cleansing line</a>. While both Pierre Augé’s lines clean your skin, the Purifiers focus on problematic skins that suffer from acne, over dryness, on any condition that makes the skin look rough or uneven. Here are the products that will restore your skin to its natural radiance:<br><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-gentle-eraser-peeling" target="_blank" title="Peeling">Peeling</a></p>
<p><br>It contains Vitamin B5, which will soothe, heal, and revitalize your skin. This gentle easer will keep your skin moisturized while getting rid of dead cells and imperfections. Use this mask once a week on oily and normal skins and once a month on dry skins.</p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-mask-cream-rebalancing" target="_blank" title="Ental ">Ental</a></p>
<p><br>Apply this rebalancing mask cream three times a week for 20 minutes to feel a fresher skin. With its antiseptic and antibacterial active ingredients, your skin will feel purified without being dry. Especially recommended for sensitive skins.</p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-douce-aura-mask-leave-on-mask" target="_blank" title="Douce Aura">Douce Aura</a></p>
<p><br>This mask will help the tissue regeneration on your skin by giving it the enzymes and hp DNA it lacks. Because of this, it’s perfect to use against cutaneous aging. Heal your skin against stress and pollution by using this remarkable treatment once a week!</p>
<p> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Let us know if you have any doubts on which purifier would work best for your clients. Also, please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us"><span class="s2">ask for help</span></a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Cheers, </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mariana</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/purify-your-skin-with-the-pier-auges-cleansers</id>
    <published>2017-02-15T11:29:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:01-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/purify-your-skin-with-the-pier-auges-cleansers"/>
    <title>Purify Your Skin with the Pier Augé&apos;s Cleansers</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/PierAugeLarge_1024x1024_f4e9cb8e-a1db-4681-92de-d43b85b53008_large.png?v=1487188049" alt=""></p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge" target="_blank" title="Base Dergyl">Pierre J. Augé’s Base Dergyl </a>is a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement and balance the epidermis’ structure, adapting to the chemistry of each particular skin to restore its natural functions.</p>
<p>The ingredients on each of its lines are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</p>
<p><br>Today we are telling you about the Pierre Augé’s cleaners, which are carefully designed to purify your skin from imperfections while maintaining its natural qualities.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Pier_auge_cream_cleanser_ental_savon_large_74465100-ae61-4618-8c64-61ef957c77ea_large.png?v=1487188056" alt=""></p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-leapsal-cleanser" target="_blank" title="Leapsal Cleanser">Leapsal Cleanser</a></p>
<p><br>This milky cleanser is recommended for the most sensitive skins. After removing your makeup. Your skin will remain soft thanks to its main active ingredient, Lanolin Oil, known for powerfully moisturizing the skin.<br>Use it before going to sleep and remove it with lukewarm water. You’ll notice your skin getting moisturized since the first application.</p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-leapsal-tonic" target="_blank" title="Leapsal Tonic">Leapsal Tonic</a></p>
<p><br>Seals the water in your skin thanks to its active ingredients, preventing you from getting dehydrated. Complement the Leapsal Cleanser softening and cleaning actions by applying this gentle lotion every morning and evening, and feel your skin revitalized every day.</p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-exfoliating-cream-tempus" target="_blank" title="Tempus Cleanser">Tempus Exfoliating Cleanser</a></p>
<p><br>Designed to make all skin types clearer, fresher, and softer!<br>Thanks to its lipo-proteins, the Tempus Cleanser will balance your skin’s hH, and will protect it against external agents without damaging your skin.<br>Get rid of impurities and dead cells in your skin by applying it just once or twice a week!</p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/pier-auge-ental-savon-cleansing-cream" target="_blank" title="Ental Savon">Ental Savon</a></p>
<p><br>Purifies the skin and neutralizes the limestone salts contained in the water that damage your skin. Use this cream every morning and night to purify every type of skin, from the most sensitive to the toughest types.<br><br></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Let us know if you have any doubts on which cleanser would work best for your clients. Also, please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us"><span class="s2">ask for help</span></a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Cheers, </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mariana</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge</id>
    <published>2016-12-06T11:29:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:00-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/base-dergyl-a-scientific-formula-for-your-skin-created-by-pier-auge"/>
    <title>Base Dergyl, a Scientific Formula for Your Skin, Created by Pier Augé</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/imgres_large.jpg?v=1481052737" alt=""></p>
<p>In 1961, Pierre J. Augé created Base Dergyl, a formula designed with the most effective molecules and active ingredients to complement the epidermis structure, adapting to the chemistry of each specific to restore its natural functions.</p>
<p>Since then, the Pier Augé line has focused on those first principles to provide biotechnological products. This means, the line brings the perfect balance to your skin, which is an emulsion of molecules, oils, vitamins, lipids, and minerals. Its ingredients are recognized by scientist to hydrate and regenerate your skin while maintaining its integrity and the products natural qualities.</p>
<p>Pier Augé holds a patent for its unique mix of pH DNA Molecule and Hyaluronic Acid. This innovation makes the line our top product when it comes to providing anti-aging results!</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/PierAuge_banner_large.jpg?v=1481052774" alt=""></p>
<p>Check out our <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/pier-aug-cosm-tiques" target="_blank" title="pier auge">Pier Augé catalog</a> today, and please, don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us" target="_blank" title="Contact">ask for help</a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</p>
<p>Cheers, </p>
<p>Mariana</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/aqua-laure-skin-care-for-your-whole-body</id>
    <published>2016-11-29T14:07:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:04-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/aqua-laure-skin-care-for-your-whole-body"/>
    <title>Aqua Laure, Skin Care for Your Whole Body</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Aqua Laure is the newest <a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/the-colors-of-the-france-laure-rosette" target="_blank" title="france laure">France Laure </a>body care line that brings you professional treatments with Northern European roots.</p>
<p>Targeted at beauty salons, spas, and Nordic wellness centers, this line is inspired by the renewal of water, glaciers, mountains along the four seasons.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Captura_de_pantalla_2016-11-29_a_la_s_13.22.41_large.png?v=1480458859" alt=""></p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-detox-firming-veil-body-lotion" target="_blank" title="firming gel"><strong>Detox &amp; Firming Veil</strong></a></p>
<p>Firms the skin and restores its elasticity. Usually combined with regular physical activities, is a powerful ally for weight loss, as it helps to reduce the body fat, redefining your figure up to 2.8 cm. less.</p>
<p>Restore your metabolism with this body milk while you refresh and hydrate your skin!</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-dead-sea-salts-body" target="_blank" title="salts"><strong>Dead Sea Salts</strong></a></p>
<p>Directly from the saltiest sea on Earth, and thanks to their mineral richness, these sea salts bring you purifying, soothing, and regenerating properties.</p>
<p>Adding up to more than 26 different minerals, this mixture has excellent dermatological results on getting rid of impurities caused by pollution.</p>
<p>Use them as an exfoliant to hydrate your skin and promote blood circulation, or dilute them in your bath to get rid of body pains and stress.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-exfoliating-effervescent-body-gel" target="_blank" title="body gel"><strong>Exfoliating Effervescent Gel</strong></a></p>
<p>An effervescent foam that liberates oxygen, activating microcirculation.</p>
<p>As it gets rid of dead cells, it detoxifies your body and promotes cell renewal, leaving you with a soft and clean feeling after a soothing body treatment.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-relaxing-mousse-with-clay" target="_blank" title="mousse"><strong>Relaxing Mousse with Clay</strong></a></p>
<p>After exfoliation, apply this wrapping moose all around your body to calm your body and mind.</p>
<p>With its variety of essential oils, it revitalizes, nourishes and hydrates your body, getting rid of muscle pains. You can even warm it up to get a super appeasing experience!</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-lipo-massage-device" target="_blank" title="massage"><strong>Lipo-Massage Device</strong></a></p>
<p>Use it daily as part of your cellulite treatment to stimulate blood and lymphatic microcirculation.</p>
<p>It's comfortable to use, adapting to your body contour to provide you with better results. Accelerates the definition of your silhouette dissipating cellulite congested zones. Use it under during or after showering!</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-preventive-stretch-mark-oil-body" target="_blank" title="oil"><strong>Preventive Stretch Mark Oil</strong></a></p>
<p>With a richness of Vitamins E and K, carotenoids and squalene, this oil protects tissues from deterioration. Heals and regenerates skin with its antioxidant properties, preventing and minimizing stretch marks.</p>
<p>A perfect remedy during pregnancy, adolescence, or gain of weight!</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-light-refreshing-gel-body" target="_blank" title="refresh gel"><strong>Light &amp; Refreshing Gel</strong></a></p>
<p>If you have sensitive skin problems, this is the perfect solution for you!</p>
<p>Get rid of circulatory problems with a gel that stimulates oxygenation of your whole body. Its anti-inflammatory properties nourish, calms and refresh your skin.</p>
<p>Apply after your professional or home exfoliation</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-multi-care-shower-gel" target="_blank" title="shower gel"><strong>Multi-Care Shower Gel</strong></a></p>
<p>The best cleansing gel you can get, as it exfoliates your skin while leaving a protective layer that provides longer hydration.</p>
<p>Brightens your skin and soothes it, always protecting its integrity.</p>
<p>Feel your skin reborn, and get rid of itchy and dry feelings right after the first application!</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/aqua-laure-elasticity_stretch-mark-body_large_large.JPG?v=1480459213" alt=""> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-elasticity-stretch-mark-formula-body" target="_blank" title="butter"><strong>Elasticity Stretch Mark Formula</strong></a></p>
<p>Prevents and improves the appearance of stretch marks, that get more noticeable with time.</p>
<p>Apply after showering, to heal your skin in particular areas like thighs, hips, arms, stomach, bottom, lower back, and breasts.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-natural-extracts-elixir-body" target="_blank" title="elixir"><strong>Natural Extracts Elixir</strong></a></p>
<p>A unique elixir that can be combines with sea salts for an exfoliation treatment or used alone for a perfect body massage.</p>
<p>Use after any treatment to feel a soft, regenerating, and hydrating effect.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-deodorant" target="_blank" title="deodorant"><strong>Deodorant</strong></a></p>
<p>Bacteria is responsible for the bad smell under your armpits.</p>
<p>Luckily, Aqua-Laure has the perfect solution for this every-day problem. This deodorant that doesn't contain any alcohol has a unique formula that makes armpits inhospitable for bacteria while counteracting the smells related to perspiration.</p>
<p>Apply on clean and dry armpits to feel its freshness all day long!</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-circadian-cryogel" target="_blank" title="cicadian gel"><strong>Circadian CryoGel</strong></a></p>
<p>A treatment that when applied acts for 24 hours, stimulating your metabolism day and night!</p>
<p>Unclogs tissues, increases fat-burning, and promotes blood circulation, resulting in a soft and firm skin.</p>
<p>Apply it to cellulite problems, volume loss, silhouette refining, elasticity improvement, ant to soothe arthritis pain and inflammations.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-dermo-performance-body-butter" target="_blank" title="butter"><strong>Dermo-Performance Butter</strong></a></p>
<p>Gets rid of damaged dry skin in an instant!</p>
<p>Protect your skin from external damages that make it look dull and unhealthy. Feel the humidity of your skin intact, and sensitive skin relieved.</p>
<p>Use it to smooth rough areas, and even on cracked hills!</p>
<p> </p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/aqua-laure-slimming-firming-algae" title="algae"><strong>Slimming &amp; Firming Algae</strong></a></p>
<p>With its high concentration of minerals, algae provide the most revitalizing effects on your skin: reduce cellulite, remineralize, firm and reshape your body.</p>
<p>It also detoxifies your skin and stimulates the process of fat breakdown, getting rid of all unnecessary and damaging substances in your skin, and making it more susceptible to receive minerals and vitamins to bring it back to life.</p>
<p>Wrap your body in algae and feel your body renewed!</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/famille-Aqua-Laure-groupe_web-1_large.jpg?v=1480459501" alt=""></p>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us" target="_blank" title="Contact">ask for help</a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</p>
<p>Cheers, </p>
<p>Mariana</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/compliment-your-wellness-routine-with-the-phyto-ceutical-line</id>
    <published>2016-11-24T12:51:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:08-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/compliment-your-wellness-routine-with-the-phyto-ceutical-line"/>
    <title>Compliment Your Wellness Routine With the Phyto-Ceutical Line</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>While Phyto5 carries a <a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/phyto5-the-energetic-skincare-line" target="_blank" title="energetic line">complete line for balancing the energy of your body</a>, it has also created the Phyto-Ceutical Line.<br>These products target specific skincare conditions with pharmaceutical quality, and can be used along with the <a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/phyto5-the-energetic-skincare-line" target="_blank" title="energetic line">5 Elements Lin</a>e, as wells as a treatment by their own.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/products_bioceutical_large.jpg?v=1480021251" alt=""><br><br><span style="text-decoration: underline;">To Cleanse</span></p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-mild-cleansing-milk-with-grape-seed-oil" target="_blank" title="mild cleansing milk"><strong>Mild Cleansing Milk</strong></a><br>With grapeseed and orange oils, is designed for sensitive skin. Its milky consistency keeps the skin from drying, while you remove bacteria, make-up, dust, and other impurities.<br><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-deep-cleansing-milk" target="_blank" title="Deep cleansing"><strong>Deep Cleansing Milk</strong></a><br>A deep cleansing milk made especially for normal, oily, and combination skins. A perfect make-up remover that decongests your skin.<br><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-phytaacid-cleansing-gel" target="_blank" title="cleansing gel"><strong>Phyt’acid Cleansing Gel</strong></a><br>Ideal for every skin type. This gel balances the pH of your face and body. It protects, calms, and soothes the skin, exfoliating dead skin cells.<br><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-facial-cleansing-gel" target="_blank" title="cleansing gel"><strong>Purifying Facial Cleansing Gel</strong></a><br>Created for oily skin, this treatment has high cleansing actions. Plus, it helps to balance the oil productions to make your skin look healthy and clean.<br><br><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Protect</span></p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/phyto-5-natural-ph-balancing-cream_large.jpg?v=1480021792" alt=""></p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-natural-ph-balancing-cream" target="_blank" title="ph balancing"><strong>Natural pH Balancing Cream</strong></a><br>Restores the natural pH levels of your skin. For its soothing and calming properties, it's perfect to apply after a minor burn or irritations.<br><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-extreme-yang-oe-cream-with-spf30" target="_blank" title="yang cream"><strong>Extreme Yang OE Cream</strong></a><br>With its antiaging properties, it protects your face from the sun,<br>Cultural fact: OE means the energy of the Sun in Chinese.<br><br><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Nourish &amp; Hydrate</span></p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-biostimulant-cream-with-vitamin-e" target="_blank" title="biostimulant"><strong>Biostimulant Cream</strong></a> <br>With Vitamin E, that helps to lift and tone all skin types.<br><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-eye-cream" target="_blank" title="eye cream"><strong>Eye Cream</strong></a><br>Designed for the skin around the eyes, which is more sensitive and delicate than the rest of your face, it firms the area to get rid of puffiness and dark circles. It leaves a smooth and healthy feeling after applying.<br><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-tropical-hydrating-cream" target="_blank" title="Tropical cream"><strong>Tropical Hydrating Cream</strong></a><br>With anti-aging properties, this cream hydrates your skin, particularly in hot and humid climates. It’s particularly pleasant for dry and sensitive skins.<br><br><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Mineralize</span></p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-algoderm-base-cream-face-mask" target="_blank" title="algoderm"><strong>Algoderm Cream Mask</strong></a><br>Facial masks that mineralize while exfoliating, hydrating and detoxifying.</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-oligo-5-face-hair-body" target="_blank" title="oligo 5"><strong>Oligo 5</strong></a></p>
<p>Restores the essential mineral content of the skin. Balances the skin metabolism, making it look healthier, cleaner and hydrated.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/phyto-5-oligo-5-face-hair-body-spray_large.jpg?v=1480021636" alt=""><br><br><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Body Balance</span><br><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-vegetal-oil-emulsion" target="_blank" title="Oil emulsion"><strong>Vegetal Oil Emulsion</strong></a> <br>Apply a small amount on your hands and massage gently in any part of your body. Tones and hydrates refresh, and promotes blood circulation<br><br><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Hair Condition</span></p>
<p><br><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-phytliss-hair-conditioner" target="_blank" title="conditioner"><strong>Phyt’liss conditioner</strong></a><br>With jojoba oil. Coats the hair with a protective balm to make it soft and silky. You’ll feel your hair revitalized, hydrated and vigorous.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Complementary to this line, the <a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/phyto5s-anti-aging-solution-ageless-la-cure" target="_blank" title="bio ceuticals">Phyto-Bio-Ceuticals</a> are the newest addition to the Phyto5 wellness solutions. They bring to you the same pharmaceutical quality and results, with certified bio elements and as always, true natural and organic solutions!</p>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Check out more of the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/phyto-5" target="_blank" title="phyto5">Phyto5 catalog with us</a>, and please, don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us" target="_blank" title="Contact">ask for help</a> if you need placing an order ;)</p>
<p>Cheers, </p>
<p>Mariana</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/tone-dehydrated-skin-with-phyto5-water-line</id>
    <published>2016-11-17T16:09:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:14-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/tone-dehydrated-skin-with-phyto5-water-line"/>
    <title>Tone Dehydrated Skin With Phyto5 Water Line</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><br>Mixing traditional Chinese medicine with contemporary Swiss technologies,<span> </span><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/phyto5-the-energetic-skincare-line" target="_blank" title="Phyto5">Phyto5 focuses on providing natural ingredients</a> like clay, algae, minerals and essential oils that renew the body with the philosophy of bringing energy balance to your system as a whole.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Captura_de_pantalla_2016-11-17_a_la_s_16.10.23_large.png?v=1479427874" alt=""><br>This holistic method brings the five elements of Chinese philosophy: Fire, Wood, Earth, Metal, and Water that harmonize with the energy of each season in nature. Professionals in Phyto5 are trained to evaluate your body condition in order to choose which of the elements is best for you, as the products don’t only focus on skincare, but the wellness of the entire body energy. <br><br>Today, we are showing you the Water Line products.<br>These products are intended to solve skin problems like dehydration, wrinkles and lack of tone.<br>It’s also perfect to use during the<a href="http://www.5elements.com/docs/elements/water.html" target="_blank" title="winter"> energetic winter</a>, from November 8th to January 10th.<br><br></p>
<ul>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-water-toning-toner" target="_blank" title="toner">Water Toning Toner</a>: With balancing properties made for Water balance.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-ceresal-buckwheat-gingko-water-day-cream" target="_blank" title="day cream">Ceresal Buckwheat Day Cream</a>: Hydrates and energizes to achieve a toned skin.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-element-water-toning-night-cream" target="_blank" title="night cream">Element Water Toning Night Cream</a>: With antioxidant and minerals designed for Water conditions.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-phytether-water-serum" target="_blank" title="serum">Water Phyt’ether Serum</a>: Serum with potent essential oils.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-black-clay-mask-water" target="_blank" title="mask">Black Clay Mask</a>: Rich in minerals and essential oils that tone and hydrate. And naturally-colored black!</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-horsetail-buckwheat-gel-water-shampoo-volumizing" target="_blank" title="shampoo">Horsetail – Buckwheat Gel Shampoo</a>: Hydrates and tones scalp. Especially recommended for hair in a graying stage. Brings back volume and shine to your hair.</li>
<li>Water Toning Bath Oil: With skin toning properties, you’ll feel your whole body renewed!</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/05_Phyto5_water_large.png?v=1479427339" alt=""></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us"><span class="s2">ask for help</span></a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Cheers, </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mariana</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/mineralize-dry-skin-with-the-metal-line-of-phyto5</id>
    <published>2016-11-17T14:21:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:17-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/mineralize-dry-skin-with-the-metal-line-of-phyto5"/>
    <title>Mineralize Dry Skin With the Metal Line of Phyto5</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Mixing traditional Chinese medicine with contemporary Swiss technologies,<span> </span><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/phyto5-the-energetic-skincare-line" target="_blank" title="Phyto5">Phyto5 focuses on providing natural ingredients</a> like clay, algae, minerals and essential oils that renew the body with the philosophy of bringing energy balance to your system as a whole.<br><br>This holistic method brings the five elements of Chinese philosophy: Fire, Wood, Earth, Metal, and Water that harmonize with the energy of each season in nature. Professionals in Phyto5 are trained to evaluate your body condition in order to choose which of the elements is best for you, as the products don’t only focus on skincare, but the wellness of the entire body energy.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/4_Metal_large.jpg?v=1479420329" alt=""><br><br>Today, we are showing you the Metal Line products.<br>This line balances venous circulation and, if your skin presents problems like dryness and dehydration, causing it to look dull and lifeless, it is the perfect line for you!<br>The Metal line can also be used in balances skins during the <a href="http://www.5elements.com/docs/elements/metal.html" target="_blank" title="energetic autumn">energetic autumn</a>, from August 7th to October 20th.<br><br></p>
<ul>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-metal-mineralizing-toner" target="_blank" title="toner">Metal mineralizing Toner:</a> With metal balancing properties and alcohol-free.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-ceresal-rice-metal-day-cream" target="_blank" title="day cream">Ceresal Rice Day Cream</a>: Hydrates and protects with antioxidants.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-element-metal-mineralizing-night-cream" target="_blank" title="night cream">Element Metal Mineralizing Night Cream</a>: A mineralizing treatment with antioxidants.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-phytether-metal-serum" target="_blank" title="serum">Metal Phyt’ether Serum</a>: Serum with balancing essential oils that cures dry skin.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-white-clay-mask-metal" target="_blank" title="mask">White Clay Mask</a>: Brings minerals to your skin while providing it with the oxygen it’s lacking.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-metal-shampoo-with-sweet-almond-oil-dry-hair" target="_blank" title="shampoo">Metal Shampoo with Sweet Almond Oil</a>: Nourishes your scalp to cure dryness and itchiness, hydrating both hair and scalp!</li>
<li>Metal Relaxing Bath Oil: Relaxes you during anytime of your day.</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/04_Phyto5_metaal_large.png?v=1479420312" alt=""></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us"><span class="s2">ask for help</span></a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Cheers, </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mariana</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/purify-your-body-with-the-phyto5-earth-line</id>
    <published>2016-11-17T13:20:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:19-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/purify-your-body-with-the-phyto5-earth-line"/>
    <title>Purify Your Body With the Phyto5 Earth Line</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Mixing traditional Chinese medicine with contemporary Swiss technologies,<span> </span><a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/phyto5-the-energetic-skincare-line" target="_blank" title="Phyto5">Phyto5 focuses on providing natural ingredients</a> like clay, algae, minerals and essential oils that renew the body with the philosophy of bringing energy balance to your system as a whole.<br><br>This holistic method brings the five elements of Chinese philosophy: Fire, Wood, Earth, Metal, and Water that harmonize with the energy of each season in nature. Professionals in Phyto5 are trained to evaluate your body condition in order to choose which of the elements is best for you, as the products don’t only focus on skincare, but the wellness of the entire body energy.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/ChDDIe5WgAAwlIt_large.jpg?v=1479417496" alt=""><br><br>Today, we are focusing on the <a href="https://www.breizh.ca/search?q=earth" target="_blank" title="Earth">Earth Line products</a>!<br>Represented in Phyto5 with yellow, this line was created to purify and refine your skin. <br>It attacks problems like blemishes, acne, and enlarged pores and promotes lymph circulation.<br>If you have a balanced skin, you can still use the Earth line in the transition period between energetic seasons!<br><br></p>
<ul>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-earth-purifying-toner" target="_blank" title="toner">Earth Purifying Toner</a>: With balancing properties and alcohol-free!</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-ceresal-millet-earth-day-cream" title="day cream">Ceresal Millet Day Cream</a>: Hydrates and protects with antioxidant properties.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-element-earth-purifying-night-cream" target="_blank" title="Night cream">Element Earth Purifying Night Cream</a>: With antioxidants, it provides you with the natural minerals found on earth.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-phytether-earth-serum" title="Serum">Earth Phyt’ether Serum</a>: Earth's balancing essential oils.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-yellow-clay-mask-earth" target="_blank" title="clay">Yellow Clay Mask</a>: Purify intoxicated skin, plus, its yellow color is entirely natural!</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-citrus-cypress-earth-shampoo-dandruff" target="_blank" title="Shampoo">Citrus-Cypress Earth Shampoo</a>: Detoxifies your scalp, bringing back its vitality, which makes your hair softer and shinier too.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-esserine-balancing" target="_blank" title="oil">Earth Releasing Bath Oil</a>: Ideal for a bath after exercising, or at the end of a long day! Removes fatigue and releases muscular tension.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/03_Phyto5_aarde_large.png?v=1479417528" alt=""></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<div class="entry-content section">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us"><span class="s2">ask for help</span></a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Cheers, </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mariana</span></p>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/soothe-your-body-with-the-phyto5-fire-line</id>
    <published>2016-11-15T16:57:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:29-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/soothe-your-body-with-the-phyto5-fire-line"/>
    <title>Soothe Your Body With the Phyto5 Fire Line</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Mixing traditional Chinese medicine with contemporary Swiss technologies, <a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/phyto5-the-energetic-skincare-line" target="_blank" title="Phyto5">Phyto5 focuses on providing natural ingredients</a> like clay, algae, minerals and essential oils that renew the body with the philosophy of bringing energy balance to your system as a whole.<br>This holistic method brings the five elements of Chinese philosophy: Fire, Wood, Earth, Metal, and Water that harmonize with the energy of each season in nature. Professionals in Phyto5 are trained to evaluate your body condition in order to choose which of the elements is best for you, as the products don’t only focus on skincare, but the wellness of the entire body energy.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Fire_element_07_large.jpg?v=1479257178" alt=""><br><br>Today, we are focusing on the <a href="https://breizh.ca/search?q=fire" target="_blank" title="Fire">Fire Line products</a>.<br>This line focuses on body problems like skin redness, irritations, allergies while balancing blood circulation and taking care of perspiration and Couperose. <br>The Fire line is represented with the color red, and it can be used on balanced skin on the <a href="http://www.5elements.com/docs/elements/fire.html" target="_blank" title="summer">energetic Summer</a>, from May 6th to July 19th.<br><br></p>
<ul>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-fire-balancing-toner" target="_blank" title="Toner">Fire Balancing Toner</a>: Alcohol-free. Refreshes and balances the skin.</li>
<li>Ceresal<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-ceresal-corn-fire-day-cream" target="_blank" title="Day Cream"> Corn Day Cream</a>: With its antioxidant properties, it protects the skin, energizes it, and hydrates it.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-element-fireebalancing-night-cream" target="_blank" title="Night Cream">Element Fire Balancing Night Cream</a>: Soothes irritated skin with antioxidants and minerals.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-phytether-fire-serum" target="_blank" title="Serum">Fire Phyt’ether Serum</a>: Brings natural fire-balancing essential oils to get rid of the redness of your skin.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-red-clay-mask-fire" target="_blank" title="Mask">Red Clay Mask</a>: Naturally-colored red, is rich in essential oils that soothe and calm the skin.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-hiarlixir-fire-shanmpoo-w-cider-vinegar" target="_blank" title="Shampoo">Hairlixir Fire Shampoo with Cider Vinegar</a>: Soothes irritated and sensitive scalp and gives volume and brightness to damaged hair from coloring and perms.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/phyto-5/products/phyto-5-esserine-soothing" target="_blank" title="Oil">Fire Bath Oil</a>: Use it to cool down in the summer or overheated days.</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/02_Phyto5_vuur_large.png?v=1479257211" alt=""></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us"><span class="s2">ask for help</span></a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Cheers, </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mariana</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/phyto5-wood-line-get-rid-of-oily-skin-and-hyperpigmentation</id>
    <published>2016-11-15T15:15:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:28-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/phyto5-wood-line-get-rid-of-oily-skin-and-hyperpigmentation"/>
    <title>Phyto5 Wood Line: get rid of oily skin and hyperpigmentation</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Mixing traditional Chinese medicine with contemporary Swiss technologies, <a href="https://breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/phyto5-the-energetic-skincare-line" target="_blank" title="Phyto5">Phyto5 focuses on providing natural ingredients </a>like clay, algae, minerals and essential oils that renew the body with the philosophy of bringing energy balance to your system as a whole.<br><br>This holistic method brings the five elements of Chinese philosophy: Fire, Wood, Earth, Metal, and Water that harmonize with the energy of each season in nature. Professionals in Phyto5 are trained to evaluate your body condition in order to choose which of the elements is best for you, as the products don’t only focus on skincare, but the wellness of the entire body energy.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/12783340_1750644791849457_1432792236_n_large.jpg?v=1479250463" alt=""><br><br>Today, we are focusing on the <a href="https://breizh.ca/search?q=wood" target="_blank" title="Wood">Wood Line products</a>.<br>Also represented in Phyto5 by the color green, this line is created for people with oily skin, scalp and hair. It’s perfect on targeting problems like blackheads and hyperpigmentation, while it optimizes the energy circulation within your whole body.<br>The Wood Line is ideal for balanced skins too during the <a href="http://www.5elements.com/docs/elements/wood.html" target="_blank" title="Wood">energetic spring </a>period, which last approximately from February 5th to April 17th.<br><br></p>
<ul>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-wood-clarifying-toner" target="_blank" title="Toner">Wood Clarifying Toner</a>: Balance your skin without drying up your skin with its alcohol-free formula.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-ceresal-wheat-wood-day-cream" target="_blank" title="Day Cream">Ceresal Wheat Day Cream</a>: Hydrates the skin and protects its energy with antioxidants.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-element-wood-clarifying-night-cream" target="_blank" title="Night cream">Element Wood Clarifying Night Cream</a>: Rich with antioxidants and minerals.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-phytether-wood-serum" target="_blank" title="Serum">Wood Phyt’ether Serum</a>: effective essential oil that clarifies the skin.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-green-clay-mask-wood" target="_blank" title="Clay Mask">Green Clay Mask</a>: energy balancing. Naturally-colored green! </li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-algae-wood-shampoo" target="_blank" title="Shampoo">Algae Wood Shampoo</a>: for oily scalp and hair. Its algae have toning and astringent properties to revitalize your scalp and hair while re-mineralizing and rehydrating them.</li>
<li>Body Algoderm – Yang Energizing: energizes your body with a warm sensation.</li>
<li>Yang Energizing Body Gel: Stimulates energy circulation. Warms up cold skin areas. Perfect for cold weathers and before sport activities!</li>
<li>Algae-Essence Bath Energizing Yang: Add it to your baths to provide you a deep, lasting warmth and a strong, energetic action.</li>
<li>
<a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-esserine-yang-energizing" target="_blank" title="Oil">Wood  Energizing Bath Oil</a>: The best morning bath to keep you energetic during the day!</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/01_Phyto5_hout_large.png?v=1479250449" alt=""></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Please don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us"><span class="s2">ask for help</span></a> if you need placing an order with us ;)</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Cheers, </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mariana</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/phyto5s-anti-aging-solution-ageless-la-cure</id>
    <published>2016-11-10T13:00:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:33-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/phyto5s-anti-aging-solution-ageless-la-cure"/>
    <title>Phyto5&apos;s Anti-Aging Solution: Ageless La Cure</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>If you’ve been looking into anti-aging solutions, you must have discovered that most of them require invasive procedures, like injections or surgeries, to get the best long-lasting results.<br>What people often seem to overlook is that there are also effective solutions that are way cheaper and not painful at all. Sadly, there’s a misconception that because these products are topical, they don’t work on the deeper layers of your skin.<br>Phyto5, in its Phyto-Bio-Ceuticals line, has developed an anti-aging kit that contrasts with these invasive solutions: Ageless La Cure, following <a href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner/phyto5-the-energetic-skincare-line" target="_blank" title="Phyto5">the Phyto5 Philosophy,</a> works holistically on your skin so you don’t only look great, but you also feel amazing!</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Ageless_slide-1_large.png?v=1480023901" alt=""></p>
<p><br>This 3-week cure provides five major esthetic actions: essential hydration, addition of needed minerals, wrinkles filled from within, age-defying antioxidants, and lifting, firming and toning.<br>You can find the whole Ageless line with us, which includes the next products:<br><br><a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-ageless-la-cure-cream-serum-kit" target="_blank" title="5 Secrets Duo"><strong>The 5 Secrets Serum &amp; Cream Duo Kit</strong></a><br>With a perfect balance of plant extracts and oils, this kits goal is to give you a radiant skin.<br>Use the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-ageless-cream-5-secrets" target="_blank" title="cream">Cream</a> in the morning after cleansing and toning and the <a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-ageless-5-secrets-serum" target="_blank" title="serum">Serum</a> before going to bed and notice how in just a little time, you feel your skin firm and silky smooth.<br><br><a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-bio-hydrating-cleansing-foam" target="_blank" title="Foam"><strong>Hydrating Cleansing Foam</strong></a><br>Cleans, hydrates, and protects the skin from environmental damage. To get better results, it balances the pH levels on the surface of your skin.Apply to wet face and remove with a facial cloth.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Phyto_5_hidratating_large.jpg?v=1478811988" alt=""></p>
<p><br><a href="https://www.breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-ageless-balancing-skin-toner" target="_blank" title="toner"><strong>Toner</strong></a><br>This regenerating rose flower water tones your skin, while it purifies it with the astringent properties of hazel.<br>Apply every morning after cleansing before your day cream.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://breizh.ca/products/phyto-5-ageless-peel-with-natural-aha" target="_blank" title="peel">Phyto-Peel with Natural AHA</a></strong></p>
<p>With natural alpha Hydroxy Acid exfolates your skin deeply, removing all traces of dead cells while firming the skin. It leaves the skin mosturized, soft, and glowing!</p>
<p><a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/phyto-5/products/phyto-5-ageless-algae-mousse-mineralizing-mask" target="_blank" title="moose mask"><strong>Algae Moose Mask</strong></a></p>
<p>Mineralize, hydrates and nourish your skin. With its high concentration og algae, almond oil, it revitalizes your skin, bringing back your younger self.<br><br><strong>Soothing and Purifying Clay Mask</strong><br>Composed mainly by aloe and calendula, and rich in minerals, this mask soothes the skin and heals it from any damage. It’s particularly recommended for sensitive skin, as it has anti-inflammatory properties provided by all-natural ingredients.<br>Apply after the toner for 15 minutes and rinse. See how your skin gets its vitality back from the very first application.<br><br>As always, let us know if you need to get any of these products on their retail or professional sizes. Check <span class="s1">out the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/phyto-5"><span class="s2">Phyto5 catalog with us</span></a>, and please, don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us"><span class="s2">ask for help</span></a> if you need placing an order.</span></p>
<p><span class="s1">Also, if you want to try out the Ageless La Cure line and test its results for yourself, we have an upcoming seminar sponsored by Phyto 5 coming up on November 25th! <a href="https://www.eventbrite.ca/e/forever-ageless-hollistic-anti-ageing-skin-care-at-breizh-tickets-27309214596?utm_source=Breizh+Newsletter+List&amp;utm_campaign=80675005a1-EMAIL_CAMPAIGN_2016_11_08&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_term=0_e4ce52259b-80675005a1-456094521&amp;mc_cid=80675005a1&amp;mc_eid=880251de51" target="_blank" title="sign up">Sign up for free today in here</a>!</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Cheers, </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mariana</span></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/light-therapy-and-ayurveda-philosophy-in-phyto5</id>
    <published>2016-11-07T10:56:00-08:00</published>
    <updated>2018-03-22T17:18:36-07:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.breizh.ca/blogs/estheticians-corner-the-spa-owners-blog/light-therapy-and-ayurveda-philosophy-in-phyto5"/>
    <title>Light Therapy and Ayurveda Philosophy in Phyto5</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mariana Aramburu</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><br>Our body is an energetic system that we must keep in balance with our surroundings. That’s why, for a start, he have to take care of out internal wellness. To do so, Phyto5 targets the energetic centers, which in the <a href="http://www.webmd.com/balance/guide/ayurvedic-treatments" target="_blank" title="Ayurveda">Ayurveda philosophy</a> are called chakras.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/Chakras_Numbered_large.jpg?v=1478544874" alt=""><br>The importance to keep out chakras in harmony is that to each one of them, corresponds a vital organ. The malfunction of one of them, might not just affect an isolated system, but with time, it can cause malfunctioning to other organs and systems. Finally, if you see your body as a holistic system, the right or wrong balancing of the chakras affect your mood and emotions that alter your thoughts.<br>As you can see, any small unbalance that is not treated on time and professionally can cause more severe troubles in the future that can be either physical or medical.<br>Phyto5 produces its line around these Ayurveda principles and with its serums and oils, and adding some light therapy, it helps you to improve the metabolism of organs that are failing, and to increase the wellness of your whole body.<br>If you are familiar with Ayurveda philosophy, you’ll know each chakra has a color assigned, and if the seven of them are balanced, the result is a white-lighted aura, indicating emotional, mental and spiritual wellness and resulting is a healthy body.<br>Estheticians that use Phyto5 know the importance of providing you products like Phyto5, that combine medical technologies with traditional Chinese and Indian to give the proper care to your organs.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1015/3607/files/h_chroma_contour_large.jpg?v=1478544882" alt=""><br>With light therapy, they use full-spectrum colors. As each color has its own frequency, the use of them separately will tune with each of your chakras. This treatment is called Chromatherapy, and it focuses on treating your organs with its assigned chakra and color.<br>The preferred tool for estheticians working in this field in the Chromapuncteur. Different from LED machines, this phyto5 light machine offers pure light, increasing its effects in the energy in your body.</p>
<p>If you are interested in a Phyto5 demonstration, you’re always welcome to book an appointment with our Phyto5 experts.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Also, check out the <a href="https://breizh.ca/collections/phyto-5" target="_blank" title="phyto5">Phyto5 catalog with us</a>, and please, don't forget to <a href="https://breizh.ca/pages/about-us" target="_blank" title="Contact">ask for help</a> if you need placing an order ;)</p>
<p>Cheers, </p>
<p>Mariana</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
